{"passage": "  Classical definitions of locally complete intersection (l.c.i.) homomorphisms\nof commutative rings are limited to maps that are essentially of finite type,\nor flat. The concept introduced in this paper is meaningful for homomorphisms\nphi : R \\longrightarrow S of commutative noetherian rings. It is defined in\nterms of the structure of phi in a formal neighborhood of each point of Spec S.\nWe characterize the l.c.i. property by different conditions on the vanishing of\nthe Andr\\'e-Quillen homology of the R-algebra S. One of these descriptions\nestablishes a very general form of a conjecture of Quillen that was open even\nfor homomorphisms of finite type: If S has a finite resolution by flat\nR-modules and the cotangent complex \\cot SR is quasi-isomorphic to a bounded\ncomplex of flat S-modules, then phi is l.c.i. The proof uses a mixture of\nmethods from commutative algebra, differential graded homological algebra, and\nhomotopy theory. The l.c.i. property is shown to be stable under a variety of\noperations, including composition, decomposition, flat base change,\nlocalization, and completion. The present framework allows for the results to\nbe stated in proper generality; many of them are new even with classical\nassumptions. For instance, the stability of l.c.i. homomorphisms under\ndecomposition settles an open case in Fulton's treatment of orientations of\nmorphisms of schemes.\n", "QA1_list": [{"question": "What are the classical definitions of locally complete intersection homomorphisms limited to?", "options": {"A": "Maps that are essentially of finite type or flat", "B": "Maps that are of infinite type", "C": "Maps that are not flat", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "To which type of rings does the concept introduced in the paper apply to?", "options": {"A": "Non-commutative noetherian rings", "B": "Commutative noetherian rings", "C": "Non-noetherian rings", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "How is the l.c.i. property characterized?", "options": {"A": "By conditions on the vanishing of the André-Quillen homology of the R-algebra S", "B": "By the appearance of the André-Quillen homology of the R-algebra S", "C": "By the non-vanishing of the André-Quillen homology of the R-algebra S", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is required for a homomorphism to be l.c.i. according to one of the descriptions?", "options": {"A": "If S has a finite resolution by flat R-modules and the cotangent complex SR is quasi-isomorphic to a bounded complex of flat S-modules", "B": "If S has an infinite resolution by flat R-modules", "C": "If the cotangent complex SR is not quasi-isomorphic to a bounded complex of flat S-modules", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What sort of methods does the proof use?", "options": {"A": "A mixture of methods from commutative algebra, differential graded homological algebra, and homotopy theory", "B": "Only methods from commutative algebra", "C": "Only methods from differential graded homological algebra", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Under what operations is the l.c.i. property shown to be stable?", "options": {"A": "Composition, decomposition, flat base change, localization, and completion", "B": "Only composition and decomposition", "C": "Only flat base change, localization, and completion", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does the framework allow for the results to be stated in?", "options": {"A": "Proper generality", "B": "Restricted terms", "C": "Unspecific terms", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does settling the stability of l.c.i. homomorphisms under decomposition accomplish?", "options": {"A": "Settles an open case in Fulton's treatment of orientations of morphisms of schemes", "B": "Opens a new case in Fulton's treatment of orientations of morphisms of schemes", "C": "Has no effect on Fulton's treatment of orientations of morphisms of schemes", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What helps establish a general form of a conjecture of Quillen?", "options": {"A": "One of the descriptions concerning the vanishing of the André-Quillen homology", "B": "The proof using a mixture of methods", "C": "Stability of the l.c.i. property", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the status of many results even with classical assumptions?", "options": {"A": "Many of the results are new", "B": "All of the results are well-known", "C": "All of the results are outdated", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "What are classical definitions of locally complete intersection (l.c.i.) homomorphisms of commutative rings limited to?", "options": {"A": "Maps that are essentially of finite type, or flat", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "Schemes of morphisms", "D": "Methods from commutative algebra"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the concept introduced in the paper meaningful for?", "options": {"A": "Homomorphisms phi : R \\longrightarrow S of commutative noetherian rings", "B": "Decomposition of l.c.i. homomorphisms", "C": "Flat base change", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "How is the l.c.i property characterized?", "options": {"A": "By different conditions on the vanishing of the Andr'e-Quillen homology of the R-algebra S", "B": "By the co-tangent complex", "C": "By different conditions on the S-algebra R", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "In what conditions is phi considered as l.c.i?", "options": {"A": "If S has a finite resolution by flat R-modules and the cotangent complex \\cot SR is quasi-isomorphic to a bounded complex of flat S-modules", "B": "If S has infinite resolution by R-modules", "C": "If the co-tangent complex is not quasi-isomorphic", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What methods are used in the proof of the new concept in the paper?", "options": {"A": "Commutative algebra, differential graded homological algebra, and homotopy theory", "B": "Topology, algebra and Fourier analysis", "C": "Spectral analysis and permutation algorithms", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Under what operations is the l.c.i. property shown to be stable?", "options": {"A": "Composition, decomposition, flat base change, localization, and completion", "B": "Product, quotient, intersection, and union", "C": "Permutation, transformation, scaling, and rotation", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does the present framework allow for?", "options": {"A": "The results to be stated in proper generality", "B": "For the results to be disproven easily", "C": "For an unequivocal support of Quillen's conjecture", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What aspect is new even with classical assumptions?", "options": {"A": "Many of them", "B": "Only the concept of l.c.i.", "C": "Only the stability of l.c.i. under decomposition", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What open case does the stability of l.c.i. homomorphisms under decomposition settle?", "options": {"A": "An open case in Fulton's treatment of orientations of morphisms of schemes", "B": "The fallacy in Quillen's conjecture", "C": "The issues with noetherian rings", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is phi in the context of this text?", "options": {"A": "A homomorphism", "B": "A flat module", "C": "A cotangent complex", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}]}
{"passage": "  We present a survey strategy to detect the neutral hydrogen (HI) power\nspectrum at $5<z<6$ using the SKA-Low radio telescope in presence of\nforegrounds and instrumental effects. We simulate observations of the\ninherently weak HI signal post-reionization with varying levels of noise and\ncontamination with foreground amplitudes equivalent to residuals after sky\nmodel subtraction. We find that blind signal separation methods on imaged data\nare required in order to recover the HI signal at large cosmological scales.\nComparing different methods of foreground cleaning, we find that Gaussian\nProcess Regression (GPR) performs better than Principle Component Analysis\n(PCA), with the key difference being that GPR uses smooth kernels for the total\ndata covariance. The integration time of one field needs to be larger than\n$\\sim 250$ h to provide large enough signal-to-noise ratio (SNR) to accurately\nmodel the data covariance for foreground cleaning. Images within the primary\nbeam field-of-view give measurements of the HI power spectrum at scales $k\\sim\n0.02\\,{\\rm Mpc^{-1}}-0.3\\,{\\rm Mpc^{-1} }$ with SNR $\\sim 2-5$ in $\\Delta[{\\rm\nlog}( k/{\\rm Mpc^{-1}})] = 0.25$ bins assuming an integration time of $600$ h.\nSystematic effects, which introduce small-scale fluctuations across frequency\nchannels, need to be $\\lesssim 5\\times 10^{-5}$ to enable unbiased measurements\noutside the foreground wedge. Our results provide an important validation\ntowards using the SKA-Low array for measuring the HI power spectrum in the\npost-reionization Universe.\n", "QA1_list": [{"question": "What is the aim of the survey strategy presented in the text?", "options": {"A": "To detect the neutral hydrogen (HI) power spectrum at $5<z<6$ using the SKA-Low radio telescope", "B": "To detect the neutral helium (He) power spectrum using the SKA-Low radio telescope", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "To detect the neutral hydrogen (HI) power spectrum at $3<z<4$ using the SKA-High radio telescope"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What method of foreground cleaning performs better in recovering the HI signal?", "options": {"A": "Principle Component Analysis (PCA)", "B": "Gaussian Process Regression (GPR)", "C": "Frequency Component Analysis (FCA)", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What is the minimum integration time of one field required to provide a large enough SNR for accurately modeling the data covariance for foreground cleaning?", "options": {"A": "500 hours", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "100 hours", "D": "Approximately 250 hours"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "How sensitive do systematic effects need to be to enable unbiased measurements outside the foreground wedge?", "options": {"A": "$\\lesssim 5\times 10^{-5}$", "B": "$\\lesssim 5\times 10^{-4}$", "C": "$\\lesssim 5\times 10^{-6}$", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "At what scales do images within the primary beam field-of-view give measurements of the HI power spectrum?", "options": {"A": "k ~ 0.005 Mpc^{-1} - 0.05 Mpc^{-1}", "B": "k ~ 0.1 Mpc^{-1} - 0.5 Mpc^{-1}", "C": "k ~ 0.02 Mpc^{-1} - 0.3 Mpc^{-1}", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "Which signal is the text concerned with observing?", "options": {"A": "The HI signal post-reionization", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "The He signal pre-reionization", "D": "The HI signal pre-reionization"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What introduces small-scale fluctuations across frequency channels?", "options": {"A": "Systematic effects", "B": "Random effects", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "Signal noise"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the range of SNR mentioned for measurements of the HI power spectrum?", "options": {"A": "Approximately 2-5", "B": "Approximately 1-3", "C": "Approximately 5-10", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What method is used for detecting the neutral hydrogen power spectrum?", "options": {"A": "FAST Telescope", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "SKA-Low radio telescope", "D": "Hubble Telescope"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "How are blind signal separation methods used in the study?", "options": {"A": "To increase the SNR", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "To decrease foreground contamination", "D": "To recover the HI signal at large cosmological scales"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "What is the primary purpose of the survey strategy discussed in the text?", "options": {"A": "To detect the neutral hydrogen (HI) power spectrum at $5<z<6$", "B": "To validate the use of the SKA-Low radio telescope", "C": "To measure the contamination with foreground amplitudes", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What methods are required to recover the HI signal at large cosmological scales?", "options": {"A": "Gaussian Process Regression (GPR) and Principle Component Analysis (PCA)", "B": "Blind signal separation methods on imaged data", "C": "Foreground cleaning methodologies", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Which method performs better in foreground cleaning, according to the text?", "options": {"A": "Blind signal separation", "B": "Principle Component Analysis (PCA)", "C": "Gaussian Process Regression (GPR)", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What is the key difference between GPR and PCA as found in the study?", "options": {"A": "GPR uses smooth kernels for the total data covariance", "B": "PCA provides a high signal-to-noise ratio (SNR)", "C": "GPR can detect small-scale fluctuations across frequency channels", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What level of integration time is needed to provide a large enough signal-to-noise ratio (SNR) to accurately model the data covariance for foreground cleaning?", "options": {"A": "250 h", "B": "600 h", "C": "5 times", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the impact of systematic effects as discussed in the text?", "options": {"A": "They introduce small-scale fluctuations across frequency channels", "B": "They affect the signal-to-noise ratio (SNR)", "C": "They improve the performance of the foreground cleaning methods", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "How large should the level of systematic effects be to enable unbiased measurements outside the foreground wedge?", "options": {"A": "$\\lesssim 5\times 10^{-5}$", "B": "$\\sim 250$ h", "C": "$k\\sim 0.02\\,{\rm Mpc^{-1}}-0.3\\,{\rm Mpc^{-1} }$", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the achieved signal-to-noise ratio (SNR) in the study assuming an integration time of $600$ h?", "options": {"A": "$\\sim 2-5$", "B": "$\\sim 250$", "C": "$\\lesssim 5\times 10^{-5}$", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does the text suggest about the use of the SKA-Low array?", "options": {"A": "It can be used for measuring the HI power spectrum in the post-reionization Universe", "B": "It is less efficient in measuring the HI power spectrum at large cosmological scales", "C": "It provides a low signal-to-noise ratio (SNR)", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What are the measurements that the images within the primary beam field-of-view provide?", "options": {"A": "Measurements of the HI power spectrum at scales $k\\sim 0.02\\,{\rm Mpc^{-1}}-0.3\\,{\rm Mpc^{-1} }$", "B": "Measurements of contamination with foreground amplitudes", "C": "Measurements of systematic effects", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}]}
{"passage": "  It is shown that a broad class of cavity quantum electrodynamics (QED)\nproblems - which consider the resonant propagation of a single photon\ninteracting with quantum emitters (QEs), such as atoms, quantum dots, or\nvacancy centers - can be solved directly without application of the second\nquantization formalism. In the developed approach, the Hamiltonian is expressed\nthrough the ket-bra products of collective (photon + cavities + QEs) states.\nConsequently, the S-matrix of input-output problems is determined exactly by\nthe Mahaux-Weidenm\\\"uller formula, which dramatically simplifies the analysis\nof complex cavity QED systems. First, this approach is illustrated for the\nproblem of propagation of a photon resonantly interacting with N two-level QEs\narbitrary distributed inside the optical cavity. Solution of this problem\nmanifests the effect of cumulative action of QEs previously known for special\ncases. Can a similar cumulative action of QEs enhance the inelastic resonant\ntransmission of a single photon? We solve this problem for the case of an\noptical cavity having two modes resonantly coupled to electronic transitions of\nN three-level QEs. It is shown that the described structure is the simplest\nrealistic structure which enables the down-conversion of the single photon\nfrequency with the amplitude approaching unity in the absence of the external\ndriving field and for sufficiently small cavity losses and QE dissipation.\nOverall, the simplicity and generality of the developed approach suggest a\npractical way to identify and describe new phenomena in cavity QED.\n", "QA1_list": [{"question": "What can be solved directly without the application of the second quantization formalism?", "options": {"A": "Cavity QED problems interacting with quantum emitters", "B": "Water molecule interaction problems", "C": "Wave propagation problems", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Through what is the Hamiltonian expressed in the developed approach?", "options": {"A": "Through the ket-bra products of collective states", "B": "Through the derivatives of quantum states", "C": "Through the angular momentum conservation", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is determined by the Mahaux-Weidenmüller formula in the developed approach?", "options": {"A": "The S-matrix of input-output problems", "B": "The behavior of quantum dots", "C": "The transmission of a single photon", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What manifests the effect of cumulative action of QEs as shown through the first problem in the approach?", "options": {"A": "Propagation of a photon resonantly interacting with N two-level QEs", "B": "Transmission of a quantum wave across the cavity", "C": "Behavior of single photons in the presence of quantum dots", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does the presented problem solve for in case of an optical cavity with two modes?", "options": {"A": "Electronic transitions of N three-level QEs", "B": "Frequency modulation of photonic waves", "C": "Rapid fire photon transmission", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does the described structure enable?", "options": {"A": "Down-conversion of the single photon frequency with high amplitude", "B": "Increase in the speed of photons", "C": "Generation of new quantum states", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is required for the described structure to approach unity amplitude?", "options": {"A": "Absence of the external driving field and sufficiently small cavity losses and QE dissipation", "B": "Presence of a strong external magnetic field", "C": "Introduction of a large number of QEs", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What type of quantum emitters are considered in cavity QED problems?", "options": {"A": "Atoms, quantum dots, or vacancy centers", "B": "Photons and electromagnetic waves", "C": "Neutron stars and black holes", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "How can the developed approach potentially be applied?", "options": {"A": "To identify and describe new phenomena in cavity QED", "B": "To predict future developments in quantum technology", "C": "To manipulate electrical circuits", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What manifests the effect of cumulative action of QEs?", "options": {"A": "The solution to the problem of photon propagation resonantly interacting with N two-level QEs", "B": "The Hamiltonian expression", "C": "The quantum emissions from vacancy centers", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "What are the examples of quantum emitters (QEs)?", "options": {"A": "Atoms, quantum dots, or vacancy centers", "B": "Electromagnetic radiation and waves", "C": "Photons and cavities", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the problem that the developed approach is primarily illustrated for?", "options": {"A": "Propagation of a photon resonantly interacting with N two-level QEs", "B": "Propagation of a photon through a vacuum", "C": "Interaction of photon with quantum fields", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the effect of cumulative action of QEs previously known for?", "options": {"A": "Special cases", "B": "All Cases", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "General Cases"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "How is the problem of propagation of a single photon interacting with QEs solved in the approach?", "options": {"A": "By using the second quantization formalism", "B": "Through the ket-bra products of collective states", "C": "By using classical physics", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What formula is used to determine exactly the S-matrix of input-output problems in the approach?", "options": {"A": "Mahaux-Weidenm\"uller formula", "B": "Quantum mechanical Bra-Ket", "C": "Schrodinger's formula", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the test case for solving the problem of the cumulative action of QEs enhancing the inelastic resonant transmission of a single photon?", "options": {"A": "An optical cavity having two modes resonantly coupled to electronic transitions of N three-level QEs", "B": "A resonantly coupled two-level atom", "C": "An optical cavity having two modes non-resonantly coupled", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does the simplest realistic structure described in the text enable?", "options": {"A": "The down-conversion of the single photon frequency with the amplitude approaching unity", "B": "The up-conversion of single photon", "C": "Quantum teleportation", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Under which conditions does the described structure enable the down-conversion of the single photon frequency?", "options": {"A": "In the absence of the external driving field and for sufficiently small cavity losses and QE dissipation", "B": "In the presence of an external driving field with large cavity losses", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "In the presence of an external driving field with small cavity losses"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does the developed approach suggest?", "options": {"A": "A practical way to identify and describe new phenomena in cavity QED", "B": "A theoretical way to predict new phenomena in quantum mechanics", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "An impractical way to study cavity QED"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does the approach achieve primarily?", "options": {"A": "Solves a broad class of cavity quantum electrodynamics (QED) problems directly without application of the second quantization formalism", "B": "Solves only specific cases of quantum electrodynamics", "C": "Relies on the use of the second quantization formalism to solve QED problems", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}]}
{"passage": "PHOENIX (Reuters) - U.S. President Donald Trump warned on Tuesday he might terminate the NAFTA trade treaty with Mexico and Canada after three-way talks failed to bridge deep differences. The United States, Canada and Mexico wrapped up their first round of talks on Sunday to revamp the trade pact with little sign of a breakthrough coming. Trump reopened negotiations of the 1994 treaty out of concern U.S. economic interests were suffering. “Personally, I don’t think we can make a deal. I think we’ll probably end up terminating NAFTA at some point,” Trump said at a political rally in Phoenix, Arizona. Suggesting a termination might help jumpstart the negotiations, Trump said: “I personally don’t think you can make a deal without a termination.” Following Trump’s remarks, Mexican foreign minister Luis Videgaray tweeted: “No surprises: we’re already in a negotiation. Mexico will remain at the table with serenity, firmness and with the national interest ahead.” In a joint statement issued at the end of five days of negotiations in Washington, the top trade officials from the three countries said Mexico would host the next round of talks from Sept. 1 to 5. The talks will move to Canada later in September, then return to the United States in October, with additional rounds planned for later this year. ", "QA1_list": [{"question": "Who warned about the potential termination of the NAFTA trade treaty?", "options": {"A": "U.S. President Donald Trump", "B": "Mexican foreign minister Luis Videgaray", "C": "Canadian Prime Minister", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "When were the first round of the NAFTA treaty talks wrapped up?", "options": {"A": "Sunday", "B": "Monday", "C": "Saturday", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Why did President Trump reopen the negotiations of the 1994 treaty?", "options": {"A": "Out of concern U.S. economic interests were suffering", "B": "To enhance the relationship with Canada", "C": "Due to pressure from the Mexican government", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Where was President Trump at when he suggested the termination of NAFTA might jumpstart negotiations?", "options": {"A": "Phoenix, Arizona", "B": "Washington, D.C.", "C": "New Mexico", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who tweeted about President Trump's remarks on NAFTA negotiations?", "options": {"A": "Mexican foreign minister Luis Videgaray", "B": "U.S. President Donald Trump", "C": "Canadian Trade Official", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Which country would host the next round of NAFTA talks after the first round in Washington?", "options": {"A": "Mexico", "B": "Canada", "C": "United States", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "When is Mexico expected to host the next round of NAFTA talks?", "options": {"A": "Sept. 1 to 5", "B": "Oct. 1 to 5", "C": "Nov. 1 to 5", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Where would the NAFTA talks move to after Mexico?", "options": {"A": "Canada", "B": "United States", "C": "Europe", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Where are the NAFTA talks planned to return to after Canada?", "options": {"A": "United States", "B": "Mexico", "C": "Europe", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "In which year was the original NAFTA treaty agreed upon?", "options": {"A": "1994", "B": "1990", "C": "2000", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "Who threatened to terminate the NAFTA trade treaty?", "options": {"A": "Donald Trump", "B": "Luis Videgaray", "C": "Canadian trade official", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What was President Trump's reason for renegotiating the 1994 NAFTA treaty?", "options": {"A": "The United States' economic interests were suffering", "B": "To favor Mexico and Canada's economic interests", "C": "Due to pressure from other countries", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What emotional tone can be deduced from Luis Videgaray's response to Trump's remarks?", "options": {"A": "Panic", "B": "Indifference", "C": "Aggression", "D": "Calm assertiveness"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "Where did Donald Trump voice his doubts about the NAFTA negotiations?", "options": {"A": "Phoenix, Arizona", "B": "Washington, DC", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "Mexico City, Mexico"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Which country was set to host the next round of talks in September after the initial negotiations?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "The United States", "C": "Canada", "D": "Mexico"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "What strategy did Trump suggest might help progress the NAFTA negotiations?", "options": {"A": "Bringing in other countries to mediate", "B": "Ignoring the issues and moving forward", "C": "Terminating the treaty", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What is the main contention regarding the NAFTA talks based on the text?", "options": {"A": "Negotiations have stalled due to deep differences between the countries", "B": "Mexico was refusing to participate in the talks", "C": "The United States wanted to exit the agreement unilaterally", "D": "Canada was not satisfied with the terms of the agreement"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who said: 'I personally don’t think you can make a deal without a termination.'?", "options": {"A": "A Mexican official", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "Donald Trump", "D": "A Canadian official"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "How did the Mexican foreign minister react to President Trump's comments on NAFTA?", "options": {"A": "He agreed and suggested Mexico may also exit the treaty", "B": "He stated that Mexico would remain firm and focused on their national interest in the negotiations", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "He urged Trump to reconsider his position"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What does the text suggest about the state of the NAFTA negotiations?", "options": {"A": "The negotiations were consistently progressing", "B": "The negotiations were completed successfully", "C": "The negotiations were facing issues due to fundamental disagreements between the countries", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}]}
{"passage": "(Reuters) - A Texas judge identified by Donald Trump on Wednesday as one of 11 people he would consider nominating to the U.S. Supreme Court has repeatedly mocked the presumptive Republican presidential nominee on social media.  Texas Supreme Court Justice Don Willett last month likened Trump to “Star Wars” villain Darth Vader in a Twitter post.  \"'We'll rebuild the Death Star. It'll be amazing, believe me. And the rebels will pay for it.' —Darth Trump,\" Willett tweeted last month with a photo of the Death Star, the giant spherical spaceship built to carry a planet-destroying weapon in the first \"Star Wars\" movie.  Willett also linked Trump to liberal Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg.  “Can’t wait till Trump rips off his face Mission Impossible-style & reveals a laughing Ruth Bader Ginsburg,” Willett posted on Twitter last August.  Last June he mocked Trump’s judgment on picking a nominee to the high court.  “Donald Trump haiku— Who would the Donald Name to #SCOTUS? The mind reels. *weeps—can’t finish tweet*” tweeted Willett (@JusticeWillett) on the same day Trump launched his candidacy. SCOTUS refers to the Supreme Court of the United States.  Asked to comment on Willett’s Twitter remarks, Trump spokeswoman Hope Hicks said, “Mr. Trump’s sole focus is considering the best potential individuals based on their constitutional principles.”  Alabama U.S. Senator Jeff Sessions, a key Trump backer, was asked on Fox News Channel about the judge’s Twitter posts, replying, “I doubt he cares.” Sessions said it was more important to ask whether Willett “follows the Constitution,” is a good scholar, has integrity and meets the high standards expected of a Supreme Court justice.  Willett’s enthusiastic tweeting would be a pivot from the current social media presence of Supreme Court justices. None of the eight sitting justices has a verified Twitter account.  Willett did not immediately respond to a call seeking comment.  ", "QA1_list": [{"question": "Who did Donald Trump identify as a potential nominee for the U.S. Supreme Court?", "options": {"A": "Don Willett", "B": "Ruth Bader Ginsburg", "C": "Jeff Sessions", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What social media platform did Don Willett use to mock Donald Trump?", "options": {"A": "Twitter", "B": "Facebook", "C": "Instagram", "D": "Snapchat"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who was Donald Trump likened to by Don Willett?", "options": {"A": "Darth Vader", "B": "Han Solo", "C": "Luke Skywalker", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does SCOTUS stand for?", "options": {"A": "Supreme Court of the United States", "B": "Senior Court of the United States", "C": "Supreme Committee of the United States", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who commented on Don Willett's tweets during the interview on Fox News?", "options": {"A": "Jeff Sessions", "B": "Donald Trump", "C": "Ruth Bader Ginsburg", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "How many of the eight sitting Supreme Court justices have a verified Twitter account?", "options": {"A": "None", "B": "One", "C": "All", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who did Hope Hicks say Mr. Trump was considering for Supreme Court nomination?", "options": {"A": "Individuals based on their constitutional principles", "B": "Only Don Willett", "C": "Ruth Bader Ginsburg", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What was the theme of the tweet where Don Willett linked Trump to Ruth Bader Ginsburg?", "options": {"A": "Mission Impossible-style face reveal", "B": "Star Wars", "C": "Harry Potter spell", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who compared Trump to the Star Wars villain, Darth Vader?", "options": {"A": "Don Willett", "B": "Jeff Sessions", "C": "Hope Hicks", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "How did Don Willett describe Trump's judgement on picking a nominee to the high court?", "options": {"A": "He mocked it", "B": "He praised it", "C": "He agreed with it", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "Who is mentioned as a person Donald Trump would consider nominating for the U.S. Supreme Court?", "options": {"A": "Jeff Sessions", "B": "Don Willett", "C": "Hope Hicks", "D": "Ruth Bader Ginsburg"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "In what way did Justice Willett compare Trump to a popular 'Star Wars' character?", "options": {"A": "Compared his presidential campaign to the rebellion", "B": "Likened Trump to Darth Vader", "C": "Said Trump would be a good Jedi Knight", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "How did Justice Don Willett express his doubts about Trump's potential Supreme Court nominee choices?", "options": {"A": "In a written statement to the press", "B": "In a peer-reviewed legal journal", "C": "In a televised interview", "D": "In a post on Twitter"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "How does Jeff Sessions suggest judging a potential Supreme Court nominee?", "options": {"A": "By their tweeting habits", "B": "By their political party affiliation", "C": "By whether they follow the Constitution, their scholarship, honesty, and high standards", "D": "By their position on social issues"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "According to the text, what's unique about Don Willett's Twitter use compared to other Supreme Court justices?", "options": {"A": "He is the only judge who tweeted in Haiku", "B": "None of the other eight sitting justices have a verified Twitter account", "C": "He tweeted more frequently than other judges", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What was Donald Trump's spokesperson's response to Justice Willet's Twitter comments?", "options": {"A": "They were hurtful and inappropriate", "B": "They showed a lack of respect for the presidential office", "C": "Mr. Trump was only focused on considering the best individuals based on their constitutional principles", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "Which Supreme Court Justice was Trump jokingly linked to by Justice Willett?", "options": {"A": "Jeff Sessions", "B": "Ruth Bader Ginsburg", "C": "Hope Hicks", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What is the relation of Jeff Sessions to Donald Trump as described in the text?", "options": {"A": "They are competitors", "B": "Sessions is a key Trump backer", "C": "They are colleagues in the Supreme Court", "D": "Sessions is Trump's personal lawyer"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What does “SCOTUS” refer to?", "options": {"A": "A political organization", "B": "Supreme Court of the United States", "C": "A legal doctrine", "D": "A legislative body"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What reaction did Willett show regarding Trump's choice for SCOTUS on his tweet?", "options": {"A": "Enthusiasm and support", "B": "Indifference", "C": "Mockery and disbelief", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}]}
{"passage": "  Human lives are increasingly influenced by algorithms, which therefore need\nto meet higher standards not only in accuracy but also with respect to\nexplainability. This is especially true for high-stakes areas such as real\nestate valuation. Unfortunately, the methods applied there often exhibit a\ntrade-off between accuracy and explainability.\n  One explainable approach is case-based reasoning (CBR), where each decision\nis supported by specific previous cases. However, such methods can be wanting\nin accuracy. The unexplainable machine learning approaches are often observed\nto provide higher accuracy but are not scrutable in their decision-making.\n  In this paper, we apply evolutionary algorithms (EAs) to CBR predictors in\norder to improve their performance. In particular, we deploy EAs to the\nsimilarity functions (used in CBR to find comparable cases), which are fitted\nto the data set at hand. As a consequence, we achieve higher accuracy than\nstate-of-the-art deep neural networks (DNNs), while keeping interpretability\nand explainability.\n  These results stem from our empirical evaluation on a large data set of real\nestate offers where we compare known similarity functions, their EA-improved\ncounterparts, and DNNs. Surprisingly, DNNs are only on par with standard CBR\ntechniques. However, using EA-learned similarity functions does yield an\nimproved performance.\n", "QA1_list": [{"question": "What are human lives increasingly influenced by?", "options": {"A": "Algorithms", "B": "Equations", "C": "Social media", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "In which area are high standards of algorithm accuracy and explainability particularly required?", "options": {"A": "Gardening", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "Car manufacturing", "D": "Real estate valuation"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "What is a characteristic of the methods applied in real estate valuation?", "options": {"A": "A trade-off between accuracy and explainability", "B": "High level of security", "C": "They always yield correct results", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is an advantage of case-based reasoning (CBR)?", "options": {"A": "High energy efficiency", "B": "Unquestionable accuracy", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "Each decision is supported by specific previous cases"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "What can be a downside to CBR?", "options": {"A": "Unexplainable results", "B": "Lack of accuracy", "C": "Too much time consumption", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What kind of algorithms do the authors use to improve the performance of CBR predictors?", "options": {"A": "Evolving algorithms", "B": "Deep Neural Networks (DNNs)", "C": "Genetic algorithms", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What do EAs in the context refer to?", "options": {"A": "Explainable Algorithms", "B": "Evolutionary Algorithms", "C": "Efficiency Adjustments", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What is the main purpose of applying EAs to CBR?", "options": {"A": "Improving classification", "B": "Improving performance", "C": "Improving algorithm efficiency", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What is the result of applying EAs to similarity functions in CBR?", "options": {"A": "They become fully automated", "B": "They achieve higher accuracy than state-of-the-art DNNs while keeping interpretability", "C": "They lose their purpose", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What is the performance of DNNs compared to standard CBR techniques?", "options": {"A": "DNNs are superior", "B": "DNNs are inferior", "C": "DNNs are on par", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "Why is it necessary for algorithms to meet higher standards not only in accuracy, but also in explainability?", "options": {"A": "Because they are increasingly influencing human lives", "B": "Because they are less expensive to implement", "C": "Because they are easy to understand", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the main drawback of using case-based reasoning (CBR) methods?", "options": {"A": "Lack of cost-effectiveness", "B": "Complexity in implementation", "C": "Possible deficiency in accuracy", "D": "Lack of scalability"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What is the perceived advantage of using unexplainable machine learning methods?", "options": {"A": "Ease of implementation", "B": "Potentially higher accuracy", "C": "Transparency in decision-making", "D": "Lower costs"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What approach is applied to CBR predictors to improve their performance in this paper?", "options": {"A": "Deep Neural Networks", "B": "Evolutionary Algorithms", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "Linear Regression"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Where are the evolutionary algorithms specifically deployed?", "options": {"A": "To the CBR decision-making process", "B": "To the accuracy measurement tools", "C": "To the similarity functions in CBR", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What is achieved as a result of applying evolutionary algorithms to the similarity functions in CBR?", "options": {"A": "Higher cost-effectiveness", "B": "Higher interpretability and explainability", "C": "Higher accuracy than deep neural networks", "D": "All of the above"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What kind of data was used for the empirical evaluation in the paper?", "options": {"A": "A large dataset of real estate offers", "B": "A small dataset of healthcare records", "C": "An extensive dataset of traffic patterns", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "In comparison, how did the performance of DNNs match up with standard CBR techniques?", "options": {"A": "DNNs were less effective", "B": "DNNs were more effective", "C": "DNNs performed on par", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What resulted in improved performance in the study according to the text?", "options": {"A": "Using deep neural networks", "B": "Using standard CBR techniques", "C": "Using EA-learned similarity functions", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What is the main drawback of unexplainable machine learning approaches?", "options": {"A": "They are not transparent in their decision-making", "B": "They lack efficiency", "C": "They are not scalable", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}]}
{"passage": "LA PAZ (Reuters) - More than half the ballots cast in Bolivia s judicial elections on Sunday were spoiled, or nullified, by voters, a sign that the opposition said showed dwindling support for President Evo Morales. Tensions are high in Bolivia after the Constitutional Court last week gave Morales the green light to run for a fourth straight term in 2019. Morales  opponents encouraged voters to spoil their ballots in protest of the ruling. Morales, a former coca farmer in power since 2006, had previously accepted the results of a referendum in 2016, when 51 percent of voters rejected his proposal to end term limits.   The citizens have defeated Evo Morales, a leader who is trying to impose re-election on Bolivia, along with corruption and the manipulation of the justice system,  businessman and former presidential candidate Samuel Doria Medina Tweeted. The 26 judges elected on Sunday will be seated in January. Morales said in a news conference on Monday that the high number of spoiled ballots should not be seen as a protest against him, but as an attempt by the opposition to block his plan for a judiciary with elected rather than appointed judges.  The unpatriotic right wing wanted the election of an organic judiciary to fail, but the people have elected their authorities; judges who answer to the people, not to politicians,  Morales said. The 96 candidates on the ballot were preselected by Congress, where Morales has a majority. Opposition leaders said the vote was a ploy to give Morales supporters control over the electoral court. Ballots were spoiled by marking more than one candidate, scratching or ripping the papers or doodling on them.  A preliminary report by Bolivia s elections authority said 78 percent of the country s 6.4 million eligible voters participated in the election and that more than 50 percent of the ballots cast were spoiled. ", "QA1_list": [{"question": "What percentage of the ballots were spoiled or nullified in Bolivia's judicial elections?", "options": {"A": "37 percent", "B": "More than half", "C": "Less than half", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Why were the people spoiling their ballots in the judicial elections?", "options": {"A": "As a protest against the ruling of the Constitutional Court", "B": "Because of the poor quality of the ballot paper", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "They didn't understand the voting instructions"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who were the judicial election candidates preselected by?", "options": {"A": "Congress", "B": "The president", "C": "The judiciary", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What did Evo Morales say was the reason for the high number of spoiled ballots?", "options": {"A": "A protest against him", "B": "An attempt by the opposition to block his plan for a judiciary with elected judges", "C": "Faulty ballot printing", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "When will the 26 judges elected on Sunday be seated?", "options": {"A": "December", "B": "February", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "January"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "What were the three ways mentioned by which the ballots were spoiled?", "options": {"A": "Marking more than one candidate, scratching or ripping the paper, doodling on them", "B": "Not marking any candidate, doodling on them, losing the paper", "C": "Marking more than one candidate, leaving the paper blank, ripping the paper", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is Morales's profession before becoming a president?", "options": {"A": "Lawyer", "B": "Coca farmer", "C": "Businessman", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What did the opposition leaders say about the vote?", "options": {"A": "It was fair and well-organised", "B": "It was a ploy to give Morales supporters control over the electoral court", "C": "It was a democratic process", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What was the outcome of the 2016 referendum regarding President Morales's proposal to end term limits?", "options": {"A": "It was accepted by the voters", "B": "51 percent of voters rejected it", "C": "It was a tie", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Who is Samuel Doria Medina?", "options": {"A": "A former presidential candidate", "B": "A congressman", "C": "A judge", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "What action did more than half of the voters take in Bolivia's judicial elections?", "options": {"A": "They voted for the same candidate", "B": "They spoiled or nullified their ballots", "C": "They abstained from voting", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "In what year is President Evo Morales planning to run for a fourth term?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "2019", "C": "2018", "D": "2020"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Who encouraged voters to spoil their ballots?", "options": {"A": "Evo Morales", "B": "Samuel Doria Medina", "C": "Opponents of Morales", "D": "The Constitution Court"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What was the result of the 2016 referendum regarding Evo Morales' proposal to end term limits?", "options": {"A": "51 percent of voters accepted his proposal", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "49 percent of voters rejected his proposal", "D": "51 percent of voters rejected his proposal"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "Who selected the candidates in the election?", "options": {"A": "The people", "B": "The Constitution Court", "C": "Congress", "D": "The Opposition"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "According to Evo Morales, why were the high number of spoiled ballots not seen as a protest against him?", "options": {"A": "He believes it was an attempt by the opposition to block his plan for an elected judiciary", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "He thinks it was a mistake", "D": "He feels that the voters are not educated"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What was the accusation made by opposition leaders regarding the vote?", "options": {"A": "The vote was rigged", "B": "The vote was a ploy to give Morales supporters control over the electoral court", "C": "Morales was not eligible to run for election", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Who were the 26 judges elected on Sunday going to answer to, according to Morales?", "options": {"A": "The politicians", "B": "The people", "C": "The opposition", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What percentage of eligible voters participated in the election according to Bolivia's elections authority?", "options": {"A": "78 percent", "B": "50 percent", "C": "51 percent", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "How were the ballots spoiled in the election?", "options": {"A": "By not voting", "B": "By marking more than one candidate, scratching or ripping the papers or doodling on them", "C": "By not marking any candidate", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}]}
{"passage": "BEIRUT (Reuters) - Russian air strikes killed 21 people in a village on the eastern side of the Euphrates River in east Syria, the Syrian Observatory for Human Rights said on Wednesday. The strikes in Deir al-Zor province were to support the Kurdish-led U.S.-backed Syrian Democratic Forces (SDF) fighting Islamic State, which had attempted to launch an attack on the town earlier this week, the war monitor said. Russia has been carrying out air strikes in the province mainly in support of the Syrian army which, alongside allied Shi ite militias, has been waging its own assault against Islamic State on the western side of the Euphrates. The separate assaults have advanced along opposite sides of the river, which bisects oil-rich Deir al-Zor, mostly staying out of each other s way. The U.S.-led coalition and the Russian military have held deconfliction meetings to prevent clashes between them, though the two offensives have sometimes come into conflict. The Observatory also reported on Wednesday that the Syrian army and its allied forces had  finished the presence of Islamic State  on the western bank of the river. On Sunday, the Syrian Kurdish YPG militia, which spearheads the SDF, announced it had fully captured Deir al-Zor s eastern countryside from Islamic State with the help of both the U.S.-led coalition and Russia. ", "QA1_list": [{"question": "Where did the Russian air strikes take place as mentioned in the text?", "options": {"A": "On the eastern side of the Euphrates River in east Syria", "B": "In the western part of Deir al-Zor", "C": "In Beirut, Lebanon", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who announced they had fully captured Deir al-Zor's eastern countryside from Islamic State?", "options": {"A": "The Syrian army", "B": "The Russian military", "C": "The Syrian Kurdish YPG militia", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What was the purpose of the Russian air strikes as mentioned in the text?", "options": {"A": "To support the U.S.-backed Syrian Democratic Forces", "B": "To support the Islamic State", "C": "To establish Russian dominance in Syria", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "How many people died in the Russian air strikes in east Syria?", "options": {"A": "50", "B": "21", "C": "100", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What have the U.S.-led coalition and the Russian military held to prevent clashes?", "options": {"A": "Mediation conferences", "B": "Deconfliction meetings", "C": "Joint combat exercises", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Who had attempted to launch an attack on the town earlier in the week?", "options": {"A": "The U.S.-led coalition", "B": "The Russian military", "C": "Islamic State", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "Who spearheads the Syrian Democratic Forces?", "options": {"A": "The Syrian army", "B": "Islamic State", "C": "Syrian Kurdish YPG militia", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "Along which side of the river has the Syrian army been waging its own assault against Islamic State?", "options": {"A": "Eastern side", "B": "Western side", "C": "Both sides", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Who had support from Russia in their fights against Islamic State as per the text?", "options": {"A": "Syrian Democratic Forces", "B": "Syrian army", "C": "Both A and B", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "As reported on Wednesday, what has the Syrian army and its allied forces finished on the western bank of the river?", "options": {"A": "The presence of U.S. forces", "B": "The presence of Islamic State", "C": "Their assault against the Syrian Democratic Forces", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "Who conducted the air strikes in Syria's Deir al-Zor province?", "options": {"A": "Russian forces", "B": "Syrian army", "C": "U.S.-led coalition", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who were the Russian air strikes in Deir al-Zor primarily supporting in their fight against Islamic State?", "options": {"A": "Syrian Democratic Forces (SDF)", "B": "Lebanese Forces", "C": "Syrian Rebels", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What prompted the Russian air strikes in Deir al-Zor province?", "options": {"A": "An attempted attack by Islamic State on the town", "B": "An attack by the Syrian army", "C": "A request from the U.S.-led coalition", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who has been conducting air strikes in Deir al-Zor mainly in support of the Syrian army?", "options": {"A": "Russia", "B": "U.S.-led coalition", "C": "NATO", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "On which side of the Euphrates River did the Syrian army and its allied forces 'finish the presence of Islamic State' according to the Observatory report?", "options": {"A": "On the western bank", "B": "On the eastern bank", "C": "Both banks", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who claimed complete capture of Deir al-Zor's eastern countryside from Islamic State with the help of the U.S.-led coalition and Russia?", "options": {"A": "The Syrian Kurdish YPG militia", "B": "The Syrian army", "C": "The Syrian Observatory for Human Rights", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Which area is bisected by the Euphrates River, according to the text?", "options": {"A": "Deir al-Zor", "B": "Aleppo", "C": "Damascus", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What strategy has been employed by the U.S.-led coalition and Russian military to avoid clashes between them?", "options": {"A": "Deconfliction meetings", "B": "Joint command center", "C": "Sharing intelligence", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Which group has spearheaded the Syrian Democratic Forces?", "options": {"A": "The Syrian Kurdish YPG militia", "B": "The Syrian army", "C": "Shi'ite militias", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What was the casualty count from the Russian airstrikes in an eastern village of Syria as reported by the Syrian Observatory for Human Rights?", "options": {"A": "21 people", "B": "10 people", "C": "50 people", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}]}
{"passage": "  In line with Pomeau's conjecture about the relevance of directed percolation\n(DP) to turbulence onset/decay in wall-bounded flows, we propose a minimal\nstochastic model dedicated to the interpretation of the spatially intermittent\nregimes observed in channel flow before its return to laminar flow. Numerical\nsimulations show that a regime with bands obliquely drifting in two stream-wise\nsymmetrical directions bifurcates into an asymmetrical regime, before\nultimately decaying to laminar flow. The model is expressed in terms of a\nprobabilistic cellular automaton evolving von Neumann neighbourhoods with\nprobabilities educed from a close examination of simulation results. It\nimplements band propagation and the two main local processes: longitudinal\nsplitting involving bands with the same orientation, and transversal splitting\ngiving birth to a daughter band with orientation opposite to that of its\nmother. The ultimate decay stage observed to display one-dimensional DP\nproperties in a two-dimensional geometry is interpreted as resulting from the\nirrelevance of lateral spreading in the single-orientation regime. The model\nalso reproduces the bifurcation restoring the symmetry upon variation of the\nprobability attached to transversal splitting, which opens the way to a study\nof the critical properties of that bifurcation, in analogy with thermodynamic\nphase transitions.\n", "QA1_list": [{"question": "What is Pomeau's conjecture related to?", "options": {"A": "Relevance of directed percolation to turbulence onset/decay in wall-bounded flows", "B": "Changes in atmospheric pressure conditions", "C": "Mechanism of chemical reactions", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is observed in channel flow before its return to laminar flow?", "options": {"A": "Spatially intermittent regimes", "B": "Periodic oscillations", "C": "Inconsistent temperature fluctuations", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the ultimate stage of the regime according to the model?", "options": {"A": "Laminar flow", "B": "Turbulent motion", "C": "A stable vortex", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "The model is expressed in terms of what?", "options": {"A": "Probabilistic cellular automaton evolving von Neumann neighbourhoods", "B": "Quantum mechanical interaction of particles", "C": "Geometric linear transformations", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What process gives birth to a daughter band with orientation opposite to that of its mother?", "options": {"A": "Transversal splitting", "B": "Longitudinal splitting", "C": "Symmetric bifurcation", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who proposed the conjecture that this model is based on?", "options": {"A": "Pomeau", "B": "Neumann", "C": "Einstein", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does the ultimate decay stage display?", "options": {"A": "One-dimensional DP properties in a two-dimensional geometry", "B": "Reversible reactions in a closed system", "C": "Conservation of angular momentum", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is opened for study due to the bifurcation in relation to the model?", "options": {"A": "The critical properties of that bifurcation", "B": "The behavior of fluid at extreme climates", "C": "The impact of gravitational waves", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does the model implement?", "options": {"A": "Band propagation and the two main local processes", "B": "Methods to minimize water leakage in pipes", "C": "Protocol for testing wind turbine efficiency", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does the model reproduce?", "options": {"A": "The bifurcation restoring the symmetry upon variation of the probability attached to transversal splitting", "B": "The interaction of light with matter", "C": "The phenomenon of quantum entanglement", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "Who made the conjecture about the relevance of directed percolation (DP) to turbulence onset/decay in wall-bounded flows?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "An unknown group of researchers", "C": "The authors of the text", "D": "Pomeau"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "What is the purpose of the minimal stochastic model proposed in the text?", "options": {"A": "To calculate the probabilities of different types of rainfall", "B": "To predict the next industry trends in global financial markets", "C": "To interpret the spatially intermittent regimes observed in channel flow before its return to laminar flow", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What is the significance of band propagation in the model?", "options": {"A": "Band propagation causes the model to become obsolete", "B": "The model implements band propagation and two main local processes", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "Band propagation has no importance in the model"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What does the term 'transversal splitting' refer to in the given context?", "options": {"A": "A process which gives birth to a daughter band with orientation opposite to that of its mother", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "A process that causes an asymmetrical change in the flow", "D": "A process that leads to the model's obsolescence"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "According to the text, what does the ultimate decay stage display?", "options": {"A": "Three-dimensional DP properties in a three-dimensional environment", "B": "One-dimensional DP properties in a two-dimensional geometry", "C": "Transversal splitting", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Why is the ultimate decay stage interpreted as resulting from the irrelevance of lateral spreading?", "options": {"A": "Because it happens in a single-orientation regime", "B": "Because it does not affect the overall performance of the model", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "Because of the lack of available data"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What can be studied through the bifurcation restoring the symmetry upon the variation of the probability attached to the transversal splitting?", "options": {"A": "The critical properties of that bifurcation, in analogy with thermodynamic phase transitions", "B": "The decay rates of different chemicals in a lab", "C": "The effects of climate change on different species of animals", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does the term 'longitudinal splitting' refer to in the given text?", "options": {"A": "A process involving bands with the same orientation", "B": "A process involving bands with opposite orientation", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "A process that leads to an increase in bifurcation rates"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What happens after the regime with bands obliquely drifting in two stream-wise symmetrical directions, according to the numerical simulations mentioned in the given text?", "options": {"A": "It transitions into a symmetrical regime", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "It bifurcates into an asymmetrical regime", "D": "It instantly returns to laminar flow"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "According to the model proposed in the text, what happens just before the flow ultimately decays to laminar flow?", "options": {"A": "The flow bifurcates into a symmetrical regime", "B": "The flow bifurcates into an asymmetrical regime", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "The flow presents band propagation"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}]}
{"passage": "= BA =\nIn .\nIf B exists , it is unique and is called the inverse matrix of A , denoted A â 1 .\n\n= = = = Definite matrix = = = =\n\nA symmetric n Ã n @-@ matrix is called positive @-@ definite ( respectively negative @-@ definite ; indefinite ) , if for all nonzero vectors x â Rn the associated quadratic form given by\nQ ( x )\n= xTAx\ntakes only positive values ( respectively only negative values ; both some negative and some positive values ) . If the quadratic form takes only non @-@ negative ( respectively only non @-@ positive ) values , the symmetric matrix is called positive @-@ semidefinite ( respectively negative @-@ semidefinite ) ; hence the matrix is indefinite precisely when it is neither positive @-@ semidefinite nor negative @-@ semidefinite .\nA symmetric matrix is positive @-@ definite if and only if all its eigenvalues are positive , that is , the matrix is positive @-@ semidefinite and it is invertible . The table at the right shows two possibilities for 2 @-@ by @-@ 2 matrices .\nAllowing as input two different vectors instead yields the bilinear form associated to A :\nBA ( x , y ) =\nxTAy .\n\n= = = = Orthogonal matrix = = = =\n\nAn orthogonal matrix is a square matrix with real entries whose columns and rows are orthogonal unit vectors ( that is , orthonormal vectors ) . Equivalently , a matrix A is orthogonal if its transpose is equal to its inverse :\n<formula>\nwhich entails\n<formula>\nwhere I is the identity matrix of size n .\nAn orthogonal matrix A is necessarily invertible ( with inverse A â 1", "QA1_list": [{"question": "What is the inverse matrix of A denoted as?", "options": {"A": "A â 1", "B": "A + 1", "C": "1/A", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is a matrix when it allows input two different vectors?", "options": {"A": "Negative matrix", "B": "Semidefinite matrix", "C": "Bilinear form", "D": "Orthogonal matrix"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "When is the symmetric matrix called positive semidefinite?", "options": {"A": "When the quadratic form takes only positive values.", "B": "When the quadratic form takes both positive and negative values.", "C": "When the quadratic form takes only non-negative values.", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "When is a symmetric matrix considered indefinite?", "options": {"A": "When it takes both some negative and some positive values.", "B": "When it takes only negative values.", "C": "When it takes only non-positive values.", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "When is a symmetric matrix considered positive definite?", "options": {"A": "When it is neither positive semidefinite nor negative semidefinite.", "B": "When all its eigenvalues are positive.", "C": "When it takes only negative values.", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What does an orthogonal matrix entail?", "options": {"A": "Its transpose is equal to its inverse.", "B": "It is invertible.", "C": "Its columns and rows are orthogonal unit vectors.", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the identity matrix of size n?", "options": {"A": "A matrix with real entries.", "B": "A matrix orthogonal to its transpose.", "C": "A matrix that is invertible.", "D": "I"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "What is true about an orthogonal matrix?", "options": {"A": "It is not necessarily invertible.", "B": "It is positive definite.", "C": "It is necessarily invertible.", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What is 'BA' if it allows as input two different vectors?", "options": {"A": "It is a positive definite matrix.", "B": "It is the bilinear form associated to A.", "C": "It is an orthogonal matrix.", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What is true for a positive definite symmetric matrix?", "options": {"A": "It is invertible.", "B": "Not all its eigenvalues are positive.", "C": "Its transpose is not equal to its inverse.", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "What symbol is typically used to denote the inverse matrix of A?", "options": {"A": "A *", "B": "A2", "C": "A â 1", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "When is a symmetric matrix classified as positive definite?", "options": {"A": "When the associated quadratic form takes only negative values", "B": "When the matrix is neither positive semidefinite nor negative semidefinite", "C": "When all its eigenvalues are positive", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What extra condition must be satisfied for a positive semidefinite symmetric matrix to be classified as positive definite?", "options": {"A": "It should be invertible", "B": "It should be neither positive semidefinite nor negative semidefinite", "C": "It should only have negative eigenvalues", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What are the columns and rows of an orthogonal matrix composed of?", "options": {"A": "Orthogonal unit vectors", "B": "Negative definite units", "C": "Invertible units", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is true about the transpose of an orthogonal matrix?", "options": {"A": "It is equal to its inverse", "B": "It is equal to the original matrix", "C": "It is equal to the symmetric matrix", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does a bilinear form associated with a matrix A yield when given two different vectors as input?", "options": {"A": "xTAy", "B": "AxBy", "C": "AyBx", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Is an orthogonal matrix invertible?", "options": {"A": "Yes", "B": "No", "C": "It depends", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "When is a symmetric matrix considered indefinite?", "options": {"A": "When it is neither positive semidefinite nor negative semidefinite", "B": "When all its eigenvalues are positive", "C": "When the associated quadratic form takes only positive values", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the identity matrix of size n represented by?", "options": {"A": "A", "B": "N", "C": "I", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What is a definitiveness of a matrix determined by?", "options": {"A": "The values taken by the associated quadratic form", "B": "The size of the matrix", "C": "The number of negative eigenvalues", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}]}
{"passage": "  The outer gap model is used here to explain the spectrum and the energy\ndependent light curves of the X-ray and soft gamma-ray radiations of the\nspin-down powered pulsar PSR B1509-58.In the outer gap model, most pairs inside\nthe gap are created around the null charge surface and the gap's electric field\nseparates the two charges to move in opposite directions. Consequently, the\nregion from the null charge surface to the light cylinder is dominated by the\noutflow of particles and that from the null charge surface to the star is\ndominated by the inflow of particles. The inflow and outflow of particles move\nalong the magnetic field lines and emit curvature photons, and the incoming\ncurvature photons are converted to pairs by the strong magnetic field of the\nstar. These pairs emit synchrotron photons. We suggest that the X-rays and soft\ngamma-rays of PSR B1509-58 result from the synchrotron radiation of these\npairs, and the viewing angle of PSR B1509-58 only receives the inflow\nradiation. The magnetic pair creation requires a large pitch angle, which makes\nthe pulse profile of the synchrotron radiation distinct from that of the\ncurvature radiation. We carefully trace the pulse profiles of the synchrotron\nradiation with different pitch angles. We find that the differences between the\nlight curves of different energy bands are due to the different pitch angles of\nthe secondary pairs, and the second peak appearing at E>10MeV comes from the\nregion near the star, where the stronger magnetic field allows the pair\ncreation to happen with a smaller pitch angle.\n", "QA1_list": [{"question": "What model is used to explain the spectrum and energy-dependent light curves of PSR B1509-58?", "options": {"A": "The inner gap model", "B": "The black hole model", "C": "The outer gap model", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "Where are most pairs created within the outer gap model?", "options": {"A": "Near the light cylinder", "B": "Around the null charge surface", "C": "At the star", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Which particles dominate the region from the null charge surface to the light cylinder?", "options": {"A": "Inflow of particles", "B": "Outflow of particles", "C": "Stable particles", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What converts the incoming curvature photons to pairs?", "options": {"A": "The star's gravity", "B": "The star's strong magnetic field", "C": "The star's thermal energy", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What is suggested as the cause of X-rays and soft gamma-rays of PSR B1509-58?", "options": {"A": "The synchrotron radiation of pairs", "B": "The curvature radiation of pairs", "C": "The stellar radiation", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What type of radiation might the viewing angle of PSR B1509-58 only receive?", "options": {"A": "Outflow radiation", "B": "Synchrotron radiation", "C": "Inflow radiation", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What is distinct about the pulse profile of the synchrotron radiation?", "options": {"A": "It requires a large pitch angle", "B": "It requires a small pitch angle", "C": "It does not require a pitch angle", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Where does the second peak appearing at E>10MeV come from?", "options": {"A": "The region near the light cylinder", "B": "The region near the null charge surface", "C": "The region near the star", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What does the pair creation near the star require?", "options": {"A": "A smaller pitch angle", "B": "A larger pitch angle", "C": "No pitch angle", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is responsible for the differences between the light curves of different energy bands?", "options": {"A": "The different pitch angles of the secondary pairs", "B": "The different shapes of the secondary pairs", "C": "The different sizes of the secondary pairs", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "What model is used to explain the spectrum and energy dependent light curves of the X-ray and soft gamma-ray radiations of the spin-down powered pulsar PSR B1509-58?", "options": {"A": "The outer gap model", "B": "The inner gap model", "C": "The pitch angle model", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Where are most of the pairs created in the outer gap model?", "options": {"A": "Around the null charge surface", "B": "Near the light cylinder", "C": "In the region dominated by inflow of particles", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is emitted by the inflow and outflow of particles that move along the magnetic field lines?", "options": {"A": "Curvature photons", "B": "Synchrotron radiation", "C": "Gamma rays", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does the incoming curvature photons convert into?", "options": {"A": "Pairs by the strong magnetic field of the star", "B": "Additional X-rays", "C": "Soft gamma-rays", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is thought to produce the X-rays and soft gamma-rays of PSR B1509-58?", "options": {"A": "The synchrotron radiation of pairs", "B": "The curvature radiation of pairs", "C": "The rotation of the pulsar", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What distinguishes the pulse profile of the synchrotron radiation from that of the curvature radiation?", "options": {"A": "A large pitch angle", "B": "A small pitch angle", "C": "A strong magnetic field", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What factor is proposed as responsible for the differences in light curves of different energy bands?", "options": {"A": "The different pitch angles of the secondary pairs", "B": "The different types of radiation", "C": "The different magnetic fields", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is suggested as the origin of the second peak appearing at E>10MeV?", "options": {"A": "The region near the star", "B": "The null charge surface", "C": "The outer gap", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does the region near the star, where the second peak appearing at E>10MeV comes from, allow?", "options": {"A": "The pair creation to happen with a smaller pitch angle", "B": "The pair creation to happen with a larger pitch angle", "C": "The synchrotron radiation of pairs", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What type of radiation does the viewing angle of PSR B1509-58 only receive?", "options": {"A": "The inflow radiation", "B": "The outflow radiation", "C": "Both inflow and outflow radiation", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}]}
{"passage": "= g ( Ax ) =\nB ( Ax ) = ( BA ) x .\nThe last equality follows from the above @-@ mentioned associativity of matrix multiplication .\nThe rank of a matrix A is the maximum number of linearly independent row vectors of the matrix , which is the same as the maximum number of linearly independent column vectors . Equivalently it is the dimension of the image of the linear map represented by A. The rank @-@ nullity theorem states that the dimension of the kernel of a matrix plus the rank equals the number of columns of the matrix .\n\n= = Square matrix = =\n\nA square matrix is a matrix with the same number of rows and columns . An n @-@ by @-@ n matrix is known as a square matrix of order n . Any two square matrices of the same order can be added and multiplied . The entries aii form the main diagonal of a square matrix . They lie on the imaginary line which runs from the top left corner to the bottom right corner of the matrix .\n\n= = = Main types = = =\n\n\n= = = = Diagonal and triangular matrix = = = =\n\nIf all entries of A below the main diagonal are zero , A is called an upper triangular matrix . Similarly if all entries of A above the main diagonal are zero , A is called a lower triangular matrix . If all off @-@ diagonal elements are zero , A is called a diagonal matrix .\n\n= = = = Identity matrix = = = =\n\nThe identity matrix In of size n is the n @-@ by @-@ n matrix in which all the elements on the main diagonal are equal to 1 and all other elements are equal to 0 , e.g.\n<formula>\nIt is a square matrix of order n , and also a special kind of diagonal matrix . It is called an identity matrix because multiplication with it leaves a matrix unchanged :\nAIn", "QA1_list": [{"question": "What does it mean if a matrix is 'square'?", "options": {"A": "It has the same number of rows and columns", "B": "It has more rows than columns", "C": "It is a graph of a quadratic function", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Where are the entries aii located in a square matrix?", "options": {"A": "In the bottom left corner", "B": "On the main diagonal", "C": "In the top right corner", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What is the rank of a matrix?", "options": {"A": "The maximum number of linearly independent row vectors", "B": "The number of non-zero entries", "C": "The number of rows in the matrix", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is an upper triangular matrix?", "options": {"A": "A matrix where all entries below the main diagonal are zero", "B": "A matrix where all entries above the main diagonal are zero", "C": "A matrix where all entries on the main diagonal are zero", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "How are the elements arranged in an identity matrix?", "options": {"A": "The elements on the main diagonal are equal to 1, all other elements are equal to 0", "B": "All elements are equal to 1", "C": "All elements are equal to 0", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is a diagonal matrix?", "options": {"A": "A matrix where all off-diagonal elements are zero", "B": "A matrix where all elements are equal to 1", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "A matrix where all elements on the main diagonal are zero"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does the rank-nullity theorem state?", "options": {"A": "The dimension of the kernel of a matrix plus the rank equals the number of columns of the matrix", "B": "The rank of a matrix is always equal to the nullity", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "The rank of a matrix is always less than the nullity"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What effect does multiplying a matrix by an identity matrix have?", "options": {"A": "It leaves the matrix unchanged", "B": "It zeroes out the matrix", "C": "It doubles the values in the matrix", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is a lower triangular matrix?", "options": {"A": "A matrix where all entries above the main diagonal are zero", "B": "A matrix where all entries below the main diagonal are zero", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "A matrix where all entries on the main diagonal are zero"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "How are the entries in aii on a square matrix oriented?", "options": {"A": "They lie on the imaginary line which runs from the top left corner to the bottom right corner of the matrix", "B": "They lie on the imaginary line which runs from the bottom left corner to the top right corner of the matrix", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "They are scattered randomly across the matrix"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "What is the rank of a matrix?", "options": {"A": "The maximum number of linearly independent row vectors of the matrix", "B": "The total number of row vectors in the matrix", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "The number of columns in the matrix"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is a square matrix?", "options": {"A": "A matrix with the same number of rows and columns", "B": "Square shaped matrix", "C": "A matrix that only contains square numbers", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is true when a matrix is a lower triangular matrix?", "options": {"A": "All entries of the matrix above the main diagonal are zero", "B": "All entries of the matrix below the main diagonal are zero", "C": "All off-diagonal elements are zero", "D": "The matrix is square"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does the rank-nullity theorem state?", "options": {"A": "The dimension of the kernel of a matrix plus the rank equals the number of rows of the matrix", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "The dimension of the kernel of a matrix plus the rank equals the number of columns of the matrix", "D": "The dimension of the kernel of a matrix equals the number of columns of the matrix"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What is representative of an identity matrix?", "options": {"A": "All the elements on the main diagonal are equal to 1 and all other elements are equal to 0", "B": "All entries of the matrix below the main diagonal are zero", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "Members of a diagonal matrix"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What happens when a matrix is multiplied by an identity matrix?", "options": {"A": "It leaves the matrix unchanged", "B": "It changes the matrix", "C": "It zeroes out the matrix", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What do the entries aii form in a square matrix?", "options": {"A": "The main diagonal of a square matrix", "B": "The off-diagonal elements", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "The row vectors"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What characterizes an upper triangular matrix?", "options": {"A": "All entries of the matrix above the main diagonal are zero", "B": "All off-diagonal elements are zero", "C": "All entries of the matrix below the main diagonal are zero", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What are the characteristics of a diagonal matrix?", "options": {"A": "All entries on the diagonal are equal to 1", "B": "All entries on the diagonal are nonzero", "C": "All off-diagonal elements are zero", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "Can any two square matrices of the same order be multiplied together?", "options": {"A": "No", "B": "Yes", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "Only if they are identity matrices"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}]}
{"passage": "  We have investigated the role that the transverse electric field of the laser\nplays in the acceleration of electrons in a laser wakefield accelerator (LWFA)\noperating in the quasi-blowout regime through particle-in-cell code\nsimulations. In order to ensure that longitudinal compression and/or transverse\nfocusing of the laser pulse is not needed before the wake can self-trap the\nplasma electrons, we have employed the ionization injection technique.\nFurthermore, the plasma density is varied such that at the lowest densities,\nthe laser pulse occupies only a fraction of the first wavelength of the wake\noscillation (the accelerating bucket), whereas at the highest density, the same\nduration laser pulse fills the entire first bucket. Although the trapped\nelectrons execute betatron oscillations due to the ion column in all cases, at\nthe lowest plasma density they do not interact with the laser field and the\nenergy gain is all due to the longitudinal wakefield. However, as the density\nis increased, there can be a significant contribution to the maximum energy due\nto direct laser acceleration (DLA) of those electrons that undergo betatron\nmotion in the plane of the polarization of the laser pulse. Eventually, DLA can\nbe the dominant energy gain mechanism over acceleration due to the longitudinal\nfield at the highest densities.\n", "QA1_list": [{"question": "What is the focus of the investigation discussed in the text?", "options": {"A": "The role of the transverse electric field of the laser in accelerating electrons in a LWFA", "B": "The role of the longitudinal electric field of the laser in accelerating electrons in a LWFA", "C": "The role of the transverse electric field of the laser in slowing down electrons in a LWFA", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What regime is the laser wakefield accelerator operating in?", "options": {"A": "Quasi-blowout regime", "B": "Maximum blowout regime", "C": "Minimum blowout regime", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What technique is used to ensure that longitudinal compression and/or transverse focusing of the laser pulse is not needed before the wake can self-trap the plasma electrons?", "options": {"A": "Ionization injection technique", "B": "Plasma retraction technique", "C": "Electron acceleration technique", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "At the lowest densities, what portion of the first wavelength of the wake oscillation does the laser pulse occupy?", "options": {"A": "Only a fraction", "B": "None", "C": "Entire", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "In all cases, why do the trapped electrons execute betatron oscillations?", "options": {"A": "Due to the ion column", "B": "Due to the laser field", "C": "Due to the plasma density", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "At the lowest plasma density, do the electrons interact with the laser field?", "options": {"A": "No, they do not", "B": "Yes, they do", "C": "It is not specified", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "At the lowest plasma density, what is the primary source of energy gain for the electrons?", "options": {"A": "Longitudinal wakefield", "B": "Transverse electric field", "C": "Direct laser acceleration", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "At higher plasma densities, what can contribute a significant amount to the maximum energy?", "options": {"A": "Direct laser acceleration (DLA) of electrons undergoing betatron motion", "B": "The transverse electric field of the laser", "C": "Electrons not interacting with the laser field", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "At the highest densities, which becomes the dominant energy gain mechanism over acceleration due to the longitudinal field?", "options": {"A": "Direct laser acceleration", "B": "Betatron oscillations", "C": "Ionization injection", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "In what kind of motion do those electrons that contribute significantly to the maximum energy at higher densities engage?", "options": {"A": "Betatron motion in the plane of the polarization of the laser pulse", "B": "Linear motion aligned with the laser beam", "C": "Circular motion around the laser axis", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "What role is being investigated with regard to laser in laser wakefield accelerator?", "options": {"A": "The role of the transverse electric field", "B": "The role of the longitudinal compression", "C": "The role of the plasma density", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What technique is employed in the study to handle longitudinal compression and transverse focusing?", "options": {"A": "Betatron oscillation technique", "B": "Ionization injection technique", "C": "Direct laser acceleration", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What happens at the lowest plasma density?", "options": {"A": "The electrons interact with the laser field", "B": "The energy gain is due to the transverse electric field", "C": "The energy gain is entirely due to the longitudinal wakefield", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What can be a significant contribution to the maximum energy as density is increased?", "options": {"A": "Longitudinal compression", "B": "Direct laser acceleration", "C": "Transverse focusing", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What can eventually dominate energy gain mechanism at highest densities?", "options": {"A": "Transverse electric field", "B": "Longitudinal wakefield", "C": "Direct laser acceleration", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "Which electrons undergo betatron motion in the plane of the polarization of the laser pulse?", "options": {"A": "Electrons operating in the quasi-blowout regime", "B": "Electrons at the lowest plasma density", "C": "Those electrons that are trapped", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What does the laser pulse occupy only a fraction of, at the lowest plasma densities?", "options": {"A": "The accelerating bucket", "B": "The ion column", "C": "The longitudinal wakefield", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What role do trapped electrons play at the lowest plasma density?", "options": {"A": "They interact with the laser field", "B": "They do not interact with the laser field", "C": "They increase the energy gain", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What mechanism does the laser pulse in a Laser Wakefield Accelerator use to trap electrons?", "options": {"A": "Transverse electric field", "B": "Ionization injection technique", "C": "Direct Laser Acceleration", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What is the impact of increasing the plasma density on the interaction of the trapped electrons with the laser field?", "options": {"A": "The interaction decreases", "B": "There is no impact", "C": "The interaction increases", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}]}
{"passage": "  We analyze a low energy effective model of Dark Matter in which the thermal\nrelic density is provided by a singlet Majorana fermion which interacts with\nthe Higgs fields via higher dimensional operators. Direct detection signatures\nmay be reduced if blind spot solutions exist, which naturally appear in models\nwith extended Higgs sectors. Explicit mass terms for the Majorana fermion can\nbe forbidden by a $Z_3$ symmetry, which in addition leads to a reduction of the\nnumber of higher dimensional operators. Moreover, a weak scale mass for the\nMajorana fermion is naturally obtained from the vacuum expectation value of a\nscalar singlet field. The proper relic density may be obtained by the\n$s$-channel interchange of Higgs and gauge bosons, with the longitudinal mode\nof the $Z$ boson (the neutral Goldstone mode) playing a relevant role in the\nannihilation process. This model shares many properties with the\nNext-to-Minimal Supersymmetric extension of the Standard Model (NMSSM) with\nlight singlinos and heavy scalar and gauge superpartners. In order to test the\nvalidity of the low energy effective field theory, we compare its predictions\nwith those of the ultraviolet complete NMSSM. Extending our framework to\ninclude $Z_3$ neutral Majorana fermions, analogous to the bino in the NMSSM, we\nfind the appearance of a new bino-singlino well tempered Dark Matter region.\n", "QA1_list": [{"question": "What provides the thermal relic density in the effective model of Dark Matter?", "options": {"A": "A singlet Majorana fermion", "B": "The Higgs fields", "C": "The vacuum expectation value of a scalar singlet field", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "How does the Majorana fermion interact with the Higgs fields?", "options": {"A": "By higher dimensional operators", "B": "By the $s$-channel interchange of Higgs and gauge bosons", "C": "By a $Z_3$ symmetry", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What may reduce Direct detection signatures?", "options": {"A": "Blind spot solutions", "B": "Proper relic density", "C": "The appearance of a new bino-singlino well tempered Dark Matter region", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What can be forbidden by a $Z_3$ symmetry?", "options": {"A": "The thermal relic density", "B": "Explicit mass terms for the Majorana fermion", "C": "The $s$-channel interchange of Higgs and gauge bosons", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What role does the $Z$ boson play in the annihilation process?", "options": {"A": "A marginal role", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "It plays no role", "D": "A relevant role"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "What model does this dark matter model share properties with?", "options": {"A": "The Standard Model", "B": "The Next-to-Minimal Supersymmetric extension of the Standard Model with light singlinos and heavy scalar and gauge superpartners", "C": "The Ultraviolet Complete NMSSM", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What do we find when extending our framework to include $Z_3$ neutral Majorana fermions?", "options": {"A": "The appearance of a new bino-singlino well tempered Dark Matter region", "B": "The reduction of the number of higher dimensional operators", "C": "The extension of Higgs sectors", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is compared to test the validity of the low energy effective field theory?", "options": {"A": "Higgs and gauge bosons", "B": "The predictions of the ultraviolet complete NMSSM", "C": "The majorana fermion", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What appears in models with extended Higgs sectors?", "options": {"A": "Higher dimensional operators", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "Blind spot solutions", "D": "Next-to-Minimal Supersymmetric extension"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What results from the vacuum expectation value of a scalar singlet field?", "options": {"A": "The reduction of the number of higher dimensional operators", "B": "The formation of blind spot solutions", "C": "A weak scale mass for the Majorana fermion", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "What type of model is being analyzed for Dark Matter?", "options": {"A": "A low energy effective model", "B": "A high energy non-effective model", "C": "A medium-energy neutral model", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What provides the thermal relic density in the dark matter model?", "options": {"A": "A singlet Majorana fermion", "B": "Higgs field", "C": "Scalar singlet field", "D": "Z boson"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What can lead to a reduction of the number of higher dimensional operators?", "options": {"A": "Z boson", "B": "A $Z_3$ symmetry", "C": "Higgs fields", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Where is a weak scale mass for the Majorana fermion obtained from?", "options": {"A": "The vacuum expectation value of a scalar singlet field", "B": "The thermal relic density", "C": "Higgs fields", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What plays a relevant role in the annihilation process?", "options": {"A": "Dark Matter", "B": "Majorana fermion", "C": "The longitudinal mode of the $Z$ Boson", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What does the model being analyzed share many properties with?", "options": {"A": "Dark Matter", "B": "The Next-to-Minimal Supersymmetric extension of the Standard Model", "C": "Higgs fields", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What is extended in the framework to include neutral Majorana fermions?", "options": {"A": "Dark Matter", "B": "The Next-to-Minimal Supersymmetric extension of the Standard Model", "C": "The low energy effective field theory", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What appears with the inclusion of $Z_3$ neutral Majorana fermions?", "options": {"A": "A new bino-singlino well tempered Dark Matter region", "B": "Higgs fields", "C": "The thermal relic density", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who is the intended audience of this text?", "options": {"A": "Students learning about history", "B": "Experts in physics or related fields", "C": "Authors writing fiction novels", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What is the aim of testing the low energy effective field theory?", "options": {"A": "To compare its predictions with those of the ultraviolet complete NMSSM", "B": "To test the theories of Dark Matter", "C": "To validate the theories on singlet Majorana fermion", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}]}
{"passage": "ATHENS (Reuters) - Tayyip Erdogan will travel to Greece on Dec. 7-8, Greek sources said on Friday, in the first visit by a Turkish president in decades that have seen ties at times severely strained over issues from Aegean Sea rights to ethnically-split Cyprus. Erdogan is expected to meet his Greek counterpart and Prime Minister Alexis Tsipras and discuss bilateral relations, security issues and the refugee crisis, following a 2016 EU-Ankara deal aimed at reducing migrant flows to Europe.  He is also expected to visit Thrace in northern Greece, where there is a Muslim minority. Erdogan last visited fellow NAT member Greece in 2010 in his capacity as  prime minister. His visit next week will be the first by a Turkish president to Greece in 65 years.  Greece and Turkey, NATO allies, came to the brink of war in 1996 over the ownership of uninhabited Aegean islets.  Relations have improved since then but they are still at odds over issues from territorial disputes to Cyprus, which remains divided between Greek and Turkish Cypriot communities living on either side of a U.N.-monitored ceasefire line.  Eight Turkish soldiers commandeered a helicopter and flew it to northern Greece as a failed coup unfolded against Erdogan between July 15 and 16, 2016. Turkey has repeatedly demanded Greece hand them over but Greece s highest court has rejected their extradition. Greek police on Tuesday arrested nine Turkish citizens who were later charged with terrorism-related offences. They are accused of hoarding explosives and of links to an outlawed militant organization responsible for suicide bombings in Turkey. They have denied any wrongdoing. [nL8N1NZ39F] ", "QA1_list": [{"question": "When is Tayyip Erdogan scheduled to visit Greece?", "options": {"A": "Dec. 7-8", "B": "Jan. 15", "C": "Jul. 16", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "When did Tayyip Erdogan last visit Greece prior to his upcoming visit?", "options": {"A": "2010", "B": "1996", "C": "2016", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the scheduled purpose of Tayyip Erdogan's visit to Greece?", "options": {"A": "Discuss bilateral relations, security issues and the refugee crisis", "B": "Discuss Aegean Sea rights", "C": "Hand over the Turkish soldiers", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who is Tayyip Erdogan expected to meet in Greece?", "options": {"A": "Alexis Tsipras", "B": "Aegean islets", "C": "Eight Turkish soldiers", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "How long has it been since the last visit to Greece by a Turkish president?", "options": {"A": "65 years", "B": "50 years", "C": "30 years", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Where in Greece is Tayyip Erdogan expected to visit?", "options": {"A": "Thrace", "B": "Athens", "C": "Cyprus", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who commanded a helicopter and flew it to northern Greece during a failed coup against Erdogan?", "options": {"A": "Eight Turkish soldiers", "B": "Nine Turkish citizens", "C": "Ethnically-split Cypriots", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who did Greek police arrest and charge with terrorism-related offences?", "options": {"A": "Nine Turkish citizens", "B": "Eight Turkish soldiers", "C": "Turkish officials", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What did Greece’s highest court reject?", "options": {"A": "Extradition of eight Turkish soldiers", "B": "Visit of Tayyip Erdogan", "C": "Improvement of relations with Turkey", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What conflict nearly led to war between Greece and Turkey in 1996?", "options": {"A": "Ownership of uninhabited Aegean islets", "B": "Muslim minority in Thrace", "C": "Suicide bombings in Turkey", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "When is Erdogan's visit to Greece scheduled?", "options": {"A": "On Dec. 7-8", "B": "On Nov. 30 - Dec. 1", "C": "On Dec. 20-21", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What prompted Erdogan's visit to Greece?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "Aegean Sea rights", "C": "The refugee crisis", "D": "As requested by the Greek counterpart"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who is Erdogan expected to meet during his visit to Greece?", "options": {"A": "Prime Minister Alexis Tsipras", "B": "French President Emmanuel Macron", "C": "U.S. President Donald Trump", "D": "German Chancellor Angela Merkel"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What region of Greece is Erdogan expected to visit where a Muslim minority lives?", "options": {"A": "Thrace", "B": "Athens", "C": "Crete", "D": "Macedonia"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "When did Erdogan last visit Greece?", "options": {"A": "In 2010", "B": "In 2000", "C": "In 1990", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What was the rank of Erdogan during his last visit to Greece?", "options": {"A": "Prime minister", "B": "President", "C": "King", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What disruption in bilateral relations happened in 1996 between Greece and Turkey?", "options": {"A": "A dispute over the ownership of uninhabited Aegean islets", "B": "A war", "C": "A territorial dispute over Cyprus", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What action did eight Turkish soldiers take during a failed coup against Erdogan?", "options": {"A": "Flew a helicopter to northern Greece", "B": "Attempted to assassinate Erdogan", "C": "Declared war against Greece", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What did Turkey demand from Greece following the failed coup?", "options": {"A": "Extradition of the eight soldiers", "B": "Financial compensation", "C": "Apology", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What were the nine Turkish citizens arrested in Greece accused of?", "options": {"A": "Terrorism-related offenses", "B": "Drug trafficking", "C": "Illegal immigration", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}]}
{"passage": "  Self-consistent, time-dependent supernova (SN) simulations in three spatial\ndimensions (3D) are conducted with the Aenus-Alcar code, comparing, for the\nfirst time, calculations with fully multi-dimensional (FMD) neutrino transport\nand the ray-by-ray-plus (RbR+) approximation, both based on a two-moment solver\nwith algebraic M1 closure. We find good agreement between 3D results with FMD\nand RbR+ transport for both tested grid resolutions in the cases of a 20\nsolar-mass progenitor, which does not explode with the employed simplified set\nof neutrino opacities, and of an exploding 9 solar-mass model. This is in stark\ncontrast to corresponding axisymmetric (2D) simulations, which confirm previous\nclaims that the RbR+ approximation can foster explosions in 2D in particular in\nmodels with powerful axial sloshing of the stalled shock due to the standing\naccretion shock instability (SASI). However, while local and instantaneous\nvariations of neutrino fluxes and heating rates can still be considerably\nhigher with RbR+ transport in 3D, the time-averaged quantities are very similar\nto FMD results because of the absence of a fixed, artificial symmetry axis that\nchannels the flow. Therefore, except for stochastic fluctuations, the neutrino\nsignals and the post-bounce evolution of 3D simulations with FMD and RbR+\ntransport are also very similar, in particular for our calculations with the\nbetter grid resolution. Higher spatial resolution has clearly a more important\nimpact than the differences by the two transport treatments. Our results back\nup the use of the RbR+ approximation for neutrino transport in 3D SN modeling.\n", "QA1_list": [{"question": "What kind of supernova simulations are conducted with the Aenus-Alcar code?", "options": {"A": "Axisymmetric, time-dependent", "B": "Self-consistent, time-dependent", "C": "Axisymmetric, time-independent", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Which models are tested for the comparison of fully multi-dimensional and ray-by-ray-plus neutrino transport?", "options": {"A": "A 20 solar-mass progenitor model and a 9 solar-mass model", "B": "A 20 solar-mass model and a 10 solar-mass model", "C": "A 15 solar-mass model and a 12 solar-mass model", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What happens in the case of the 20 solar-mass progenitor like model?", "options": {"A": "It does not explode with the employed simplified set of neutrino opacities", "B": "It explodes", "C": "The model becomes unstable", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What kind of variations can be higher with RbR+ transport in 3D?", "options": {"A": "Local and instantaneous variations of neutrino fluxes and heating rates", "B": "Global and averaged variations", "C": "Fluctuations in stellar formation rates", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Why are the time-averaged quantities very similar to FMD results?", "options": {"A": "Because of the absence of a fixed, artificial symmetry axis that channels the flow", "B": "Because of the presence of a fixed, artificial symmetry axis that channels the flow", "C": "Because of the very high solar mass of the model", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What has more impact than the differences by the two transport treatments?", "options": {"A": "Higher spatial resolution", "B": "Lower spatial resolution", "C": "The type of supernova simulation", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What can the RbR+ approximation foster?", "options": {"A": "Explosions in 2D", "B": "Explosions in 3D", "C": "The transition of a star into a black hole", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What kind of results are very similar for 3D simulations with FMD and RbR+ transport?", "options": {"A": "The neutrino signals and the post-bounce evolution", "B": "The initial and final states of the star", "C": "The axis of symmetry and the overall evolution", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What can trigger explosions in 2D models?", "options": {"A": "Powerful axial sloshing of the stalled shock due to the standing accretion shock instability", "B": "Random fluctuations in the neutrino signals", "C": "Changes in the spatial resolution", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does the result of 3D SN simulations support?", "options": {"A": "The use of the RbR+ approximation for neutrino transport in 3D SN modeling", "B": "The use of the FMD transport for neutrino transport in 3D SN modeling", "C": "The use of the RbR+ approximation for neutrino transport in 2D SN modeling", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "What is the primary tool used in the simulations mentioned?", "options": {"A": "A 2D simulator", "B": "Aenus-Alcar code", "C": "A solar mass calculator", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What difference is there between the results drawn from fully multidimensional (FMD) neutrino transport and the ray-by-ray-plus (RbR+) approximation?", "options": {"A": "There were no differences", "B": "The results were starkly different", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "RbR+ approximation resulted in more powerful explosions"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What condition has to be met for the RbR+ approximation to foster explosions in 2D?", "options": {"A": "The need for a fixed symmetry axis", "B": "The presence of axial sloshing of the stalled shock due to the SASI", "C": "The application of a two-moment solver", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Which one impacts more on the results: higher spatial resolution or different transport treatments?", "options": {"A": "Different transport treatments", "B": "Higher spatial resolution", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "Both equally contribute"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What type of transport is the RbR+ approximation used for in 3D SN modeling?", "options": {"A": "Neutrino transport", "B": "Sunlight transport", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "Matter transport"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What are compared for the first time in these simulations?", "options": {"A": "Calculations with fully multi-dimensional (FMD) neutrino transport and the ray-by-ray-plus (RbR+) approximation", "B": "Different supernova simulations in three spatial dimensions", "C": "The effects of SASI on 2D vs 3D simulations", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "In a 3D simulation with RbR+ transport, what is the nature of variations in neutrino fluxes and heating rates?", "options": {"A": "They are consistently low", "B": "There are no variations", "C": "They can still be considerably higher, but time-averaged quantities are similar to FMD results", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What is the outcome of 20 solar-mass progenitor simulations?", "options": {"A": "They do not explode with the employed simplified set of neutrino opacities", "B": "They always explode", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "They result in powerful axial sloshing"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "In the research, what distinguishes 3D and 2D simulations in terms of their outcomes with the RbR+ approximation?", "options": {"A": "2D simulations foster high-energy explosions", "B": "In 3D simulations, the effects of RbR+ transport are less definitive than in 2D simulations", "C": "In 2D simulations, the RbR+ approximation cannot create explosions", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Which scenario explored the exploding 9 solar-mass model?", "options": {"A": "Simulations employing a complex set of neutrino opacities", "B": "3D results with FMD and RbR+ transport", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "2D simulations"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}]}
{"passage": "  Deep neural networks are vulnerable to adversarial attacks. Among different\nattack settings, the most challenging yet the most practical one is the\nhard-label setting where the attacker only has access to the hard-label output\n(prediction label) of the target model. Previous attempts are neither effective\nenough in terms of attack success rate nor efficient enough in terms of query\ncomplexity under the widely used $L_\\infty$ norm threat model. In this paper,\nwe present the Ray Searching attack (RayS), which greatly improves the\nhard-label attack effectiveness as well as efficiency. Unlike previous works,\nwe reformulate the continuous problem of finding the closest decision boundary\ninto a discrete problem that does not require any zeroth-order gradient\nestimation. In the meantime, all unnecessary searches are eliminated via a fast\ncheck step. This significantly reduces the number of queries needed for our\nhard-label attack. Moreover, interestingly, we found that the proposed RayS\nattack can also be used as a sanity check for possible \"falsely robust\" models.\nOn several recently proposed defenses that claim to achieve the\nstate-of-the-art robust accuracy, our attack method demonstrates that the\ncurrent white-box/black-box attacks could still give a false sense of security\nand the robust accuracy drop between the most popular PGD attack and RayS\nattack could be as large as $28\\%$. We believe that our proposed RayS attack\ncould help identify falsely robust models that beat most white-box/black-box\nattacks.\n", "QA1_list": [{"question": "What are deep neural networks vulnerable to?", "options": {"A": "Adversarial attacks", "B": "Low-memory attacks", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "Virus attacks"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the most challenging and practical attack setting mentioned in the text?", "options": {"A": "Low-label setting", "B": "Hard-label setting", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "High-label setting"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What are previous attempts of handling attack settings considered to be?", "options": {"A": "Effective and efficient", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "Neither effective nor efficient", "D": "Effective but not efficient"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What new attack method is proposed in the paper?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "Blue Searching attack", "C": "Path Searching attack", "D": "Ray Searching attack"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "How does the Ray Searching attack improve upon previous methods?", "options": {"A": "By increasing the number of queries", "B": "By improving the hard-label attack effectiveness and efficiency", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "By reducing the hard-label attack effectiveness"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What does the Ray Searching attack do differently from previous works?", "options": {"A": "It reformulates the problem into a discrete problem", "B": "It increases the query complexity", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "It maintains the same approach to the problem"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is one advantage of the Ray Searching attack in terms of queries?", "options": {"A": "It increases the number of queries", "B": "It significantly reduces the queries", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "It maintains the number of queries"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Apart from being a method of attack, what else can the Ray Searching attack be used for?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "For improving model efficiency", "C": "As a sanity check for possible 'falsely robust' models", "D": "As a method of boosting model performance"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What does the Ray Searching attack demonstrate about the current white-box/black-box attacks?", "options": {"A": "They can still give a false sense of security", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "They are completely secure", "D": "They cannot give a false sense of security"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does the text suggest about the Ray Searching attack's role in identifying model robustness?", "options": {"A": "It can make false positives less likely", "B": "It can help identify falsely robust models", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "It has no role in identifying model robustness"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "What do the authors claim their attack, RayS, can be used for besides the main attack mechanism?", "options": {"A": "Generating training data for new models", "B": "As a sanity check for possible 'falsely robust' models", "C": "Detecting data leakage in existing models", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What is the primary problem RayS is attempting to address?", "options": {"A": "The lack of interpretability of deep neural networks", "B": "The inability of current attacks to be both effective and efficient against hard-label deep learning models", "C": "The lack of robustness in current attack methods", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Why is the hard-label attack setting considered challenging?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "Because it requires tons of computational resources", "C": "Because the attacker only has access to the hard-label output of the target model", "D": "Because it involves handling large amounts of data"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "Why is the RayS attack considered more efficient?", "options": {"A": "Because it eliminates all unnecessary searches via a fast check step", "B": "Because it runs on low-power computing nodes", "C": "Because it requires fewer memory usage", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the primary way in which the RayS attack differs from previous methods?", "options": {"A": "It reformulates the problem of finding the closest decision boundary into a discrete problem", "B": "It uses a unique mathematical approach that no one else has used", "C": "It uses brute force to attack the model", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What do the authors imply might be a consequence of using established attack methods such as white-box/black-box attacks?", "options": {"A": "These methods may give a false sense of security", "B": "These methods might fail to attack models effectively", "C": "These methods are too computationally intensive", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does the RayS attack not require in contrast to previous methods?", "options": {"A": "High computing power", "B": "Any zeroth-order gradient estimation", "C": "Deep learning model architecture", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What do the authors suggest could be the maximum robust accuracy drop between the most popular PGD attack and RayS attack?", "options": {"A": "5%", "B": "15%", "C": "50%", "D": "28%"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "How do the authors suggest their proposed RayS attack could be contributing to the field?", "options": {"A": "By improving model interpretability", "B": "By creating a new type of neural network", "C": "By helping to identify falsely robust models that beat most white-box/black-box attacks", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "According to the authors, how efficient are the current attack methods under the $L_\\infty$ norm threat model?", "options": {"A": "Quite efficient with very low query complexity", "B": "Not efficient enough in terms of query complexity", "C": "They don't mention anything about the efficiency of current attack methods", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}]}
{"passage": "LONDON/WASHINGTON (Reuters) - U.S. Democratic presidential front-runner Hillary Clinton wants Britain to stay in the European Union, her campaign said on Saturday, following an intervention from U.S. President Barack Obama who urged Britons to vote to remain. “Hillary Clinton believes that transatlantic cooperation is essential, and that cooperation is strongest when Europe is united. She has always valued a strong United Kingdom in a strong EU. And she values a strong British voice in the EU,” Clinton senior policy adviser Jake Sullivan said in a statement provided to Reuters.  Clinton, who spent four years as U.S. secretary of state during Obama’s first term, has made her foreign policy credentials a central piece of her campaign for president in the November 2016 race for the White House.  Clinton’s position on the EU was first reported by Britain’s Observer newspaper.  Obama, who will leave Britain on Sunday, sparked a row during his three-day trip by bluntly telling Britain it should remain in the European Union to preserve its remaining global clout. He angered critics of the EU on Friday by warning that Britain would be at “the back of the queue” for a trade deal if it left the club - one of the strongest U.S. interventions in the affairs of a western European democracy since the Cold War. ", "QA1_list": [{"question": "Who is the Democratic presidential front-runner mentioned in the text?", "options": {"A": "Barack Obama", "B": "Jake Sullivan", "C": "Hillary Clinton", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What was Hillary Clinton's stance on Britain's position within the European Union?", "options": {"A": "She wants Britain to leave the EU", "B": "She values a strong British voice in the EU", "C": "She is against Britain in the EU", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Who was the U.S. secretary of state during Obama’s first term?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "Jake Sullivan", "C": "Barack Obama", "D": "Hillary Clinton"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "When was Hillary Clinton’s campaign for president?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "November 2016", "C": "Saturday", "D": "During Obama’s three-day trip"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Whose viewpoint about Britain's position in the European Union was first reported by Britain’s Observer newspaper?", "options": {"A": "Hillary Clinton's", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "Jake Sullivan's", "D": "Barack Obama's"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "When was Barack Obama's trip to Britain?", "options": {"A": "In November 2016", "B": "On Friday", "C": "During Hillary Clinton's campaign", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "According to Obama's intervetion, what will happen if Britain exits the EU?", "options": {"A": "Britain will lose its global influence", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "Britain will have stronger cooperation with the US", "D": "Britain can influence the US presidential elections"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What did Hillary Clinton focus on in her campaign for president?", "options": {"A": "Foreign policy credentials", "B": "The United Kingdom’s affairs", "C": "U.S. intervention in European democracies", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who is Jake Sullivan in the context of the text?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "Hillary Clinton's Senior Policy Adviser", "C": "The previous U.S. Secretary of State", "D": "The President of the United States"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What was Barack Obama's message to the critics of the EU in Britain?", "options": {"A": "Britain should leave the EU to increase its global clout", "B": "Britain should remain in EU to maintain its global influence", "C": "Britain should not listen to the US opinions", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "Who is the Democratic presidential front-runner mentioned in the text?", "options": {"A": "Barack Obama", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "Hillary Clinton", "D": "Jake Sullivan"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "Which country is Hillary Clinton urging to stay in the European Union?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "United States", "C": "France", "D": "Britain"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "Who is Jake Sullivan in relation to Hillary Clinton?", "options": {"A": "European Union representative", "B": "Clinton senior policy adviser", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "Previous U.S. President"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What is one position Hillary Clinton held before becoming a presidential candidate?", "options": {"A": "U.S. Secretary of State", "B": "U.S. President", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "British Prime Minister"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What warning did Barack Obama give Britain about if it left the EU?", "options": {"A": "It would lose global clout", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "It would be at the back of the queue for a trade deal", "D": "It would have stronger relation with U.S."}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What is central to Hillary Clinton’s campaign for president?", "options": {"A": "Her financial policies", "B": "Her foreign policy credentials", "C": "Her healthcare reform", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Why does Hillary Clinton value a united Europe?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "Because it reduces the likelihood of war", "C": "For stronger transatlantic cooperation", "D": "Because it improves trade relations with the U.S"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "Which newspaper first reported Clinton’s position on the EU?", "options": {"A": "New York Times", "B": "Washington Post", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "Britain’s Observer"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "What did President Obama do to stir controversy during his three-day trip?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "Urged Britons to vote to remain in the EU", "C": "Cautioned Britain about leaving the EU", "D": "Both B and C"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "When did Hillary Clinton serve as U.S. secretary of state?", "options": {"A": "During Obama’s second term", "B": "During Obama’s first term", "C": "Before Obama's presidency", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}]}
{"passage": "  During the evolution of rotating first stars, which initially consisted of\nonly hydrogen and helium, CNO elements may emerge to their surface. These stars\nmay therefore have winds that are driven only by CNO elements. We study weak\nwind effects (Gayley-Owocki heating and multicomponent effects) in stellar\nwinds of first generation stars driven purely by CNO elements. We apply our\nNLTE multicomponent models and hydrodynamical simulations. The multicomponent\neffects (frictional heating and decoupling) are important particularly for low\nmetallicity winds, but they influence mass loss rate only if they cause\ndecoupling for velocities lower than the escape velocity. The multicomponent\neffects also modify the feedback from first stars. As a result of the\ndecoupling of radiatively accelerated metals from hydrogen and helium, the\nfirst low-energy cosmic ray particles are generated. We study the interaction\nof these particles with the interstellar medium concluding that these particles\neasily penetrate the interstellar medium of a given minihalo. We discuss the\ncharging of the first stars by means of their winds. Gayley-Owocki heating,\nfrictional heating, and the decoupling of wind components occur in the winds of\nevolved low-metallicity stars and the solar metallicity main-sequence stars.\n", "QA1_list": [{"question": "What elements did the first rotating stars initially consist of?", "options": {"A": "Only hydrogen and helium", "B": "Hydrogen, helium, and CNO elements", "C": "Only CNO elements", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What elements may drive the winds of first stars?", "options": {"A": "Hydrogen and Helium", "B": "CNO elements", "C": "Oxygen and Nitrogen", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What were the weak wind effects studied in the first generation stars?", "options": {"A": "Gayley-Owocki heating and multicomponent effects", "B": "Harmony-Glee heating and single component effects", "C": "Sunspot and solar flare effects", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What are the multicomponent effects in the context of the stellar winds?", "options": {"A": "Frictional heating and decoupling", "B": "Condensation and evaporation", "C": "Ionization and recombination", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "When do multicomponent effects influence mass loss rate?", "options": {"A": "When they cause decoupling for velocities lower than the escape velocity", "B": "When they cause decoupling for velocities higher than the escape velocity", "C": "When the gravitational pull of the star decreases", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "How are the first low-energy cosmic ray particles generated?", "options": {"A": "By the decoupling of radiatively accelerated metals from hydrogen and helium", "B": "By the collison of CNO elements", "C": "By the nuclear fusion in the core of the star", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Can the first low-energy cosmic ray particles easily penetrate the interstellar medium of a given minihalo?", "options": {"A": "Yes", "B": "No", "C": "Only with high speed", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What processes occur in the winds of evolved low-metallicity stars and the solar metallicity main-sequence stars?", "options": {"A": "Gayley-Owocki heating, frictional heating, and the decoupling of wind components", "B": "Condensation, precipitation, and evaporation", "C": "Fusion, fission, and ionization", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is studied in the interaction of these particles with the interstellar medium?", "options": {"A": "Their ability to easily penetrate the interstellar medium of a given minihalo", "B": "Their effect on the formation of nebulae", "C": "Their influence on the galactic rotation curve", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "How are the first stars charged?", "options": {"A": "By means of their winds", "B": "By means of the cosmic microwave background radiation", "C": "By means of the rotation", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "What elements did the first stars initially consist of?", "options": {"A": "Hydrogen and helium", "B": "Carbon, Nitrogen, and Oxygen", "C": "Iron and nickel", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What are the effects in stellar winds of first generation stars driven purely by CNO elements?", "options": {"A": "Gayley-Owocki heating and multicomponent effects", "B": "Magnetic interference and infrared radiation", "C": "Pulsations and radial velocity changes", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "In what situation do multicomponent effects influence the mass loss rate?", "options": {"A": "If they cause decoupling for velocities lower than the escape velocity", "B": "If they cause accelerated rotation of the stars", "C": "If they increase the luminosity of the stars", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is generated as a result of the decoupling of radiatively accelerated metals from hydrogen and helium?", "options": {"A": "First low-energy cosmic ray particles", "B": "Magnetic disturbances in the interstellar medium", "C": "Energy pulses observable from earth", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What happens with these generated particles in relation to the interstellar medium?", "options": {"A": "These particles easily penetrate the interstellar medium of a given minihalo", "B": "These particles are deflected by the interstellar medium", "C": "These particles form a vortex in the interstellar medium", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is one of the mechanisms suggested for charging the first stars?", "options": {"A": "Through their winds", "B": "Through solar flares", "C": "Through interactions with nearby galaxies", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What effects occur in the winds of evolved low-metallicity stars and solar metallicity main sequence stars?", "options": {"A": "Gayley-Owocki heating, frictional heating, and the decoupling of wind components", "B": "UV radiation, X-ray emissions, and plasma waves", "C": "Flare production, solar wind intensification, and blueshifts", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What are the specific components driving the winds of the first stars?", "options": {"A": "CNO elements", "B": "Hydrogen and helium", "C": "Gaseous mixtures", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Where do the multicomponent effects, like frictional heating and decoupling, exert the most influence?", "options": {"A": "Particularly for low metallicity winds", "B": "In high metallicity winds", "C": "In equilibrium with other elemental constituents", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "How does the interaction of the first low-energy cosmic ray particles with the interstellar medium take place?", "options": {"A": "These particles easily penetrate the interstellar medium of a given minihalo", "B": "These particles repelled by the interstellar medium", "C": "These particles cause disturbances in the interstellar medium", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}]}
{"passage": "AUSTIN, Texas (Reuters) - Former Democratic U.S. Vice President Joe Biden said on Sunday in one of his first major speeches since leaving office this year that he would have liked to have been the U.S. president who ended cancer as we know it. Biden, whose son Beau died from brain cancer in 2015, delivered an emotional speech at the South by Southwest technology summit in Austin, Texas, about continuing the work he led under former Democratic President Barack Obama in the so-called “Cancer Moonshot,” an initiative aimed at speeding up research into new cancer therapies. He spoke of the need for prevention, research collaboration and big data to battle cancer. Biden did not mention U.S. Republican President Donald Trump by name but said in the speech before several thousand people he was willing to work with the current administration on the fight against cancer, which kills an estimated 600,000 Americans a year. “The only bipartisan thing left in America is the fight against cancer,” he said. Biden said that just before he made his formal announcement in 2015 not to run, Obama asked him if he had any regrets.  Biden said he told Obama: “I would have loved to have been the president who presided over the end of cancer as we know it.” He said in the months that followed his son’s death, he did not have the stomach to run for president. “No one should ever run for president of the United States unless they are prepared to give every, every ounce of their energy,” he said. He praised Republicans for working with Democrats on the fight against cancer while he was in office. He had one slight dig at the Trump administration by suggesting some “in the new outfit” do not abide by research on global warming. “I shouldn’t have said that but it frustrates me,” he said. ", "QA1_list": [{"question": "When did Joe Biden give one of his first major speeches after leaving office?", "options": {"A": "On Sunday", "B": "On Monday", "C": "On Wednesday", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What initiative did Joe Biden lead under Barack Obama?", "options": {"A": "The Cancer Moonshot", "B": "The Space Initiative", "C": "The War on Drugs", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What subject did Biden mention in his speech without naming someone specifically?", "options": {"A": "U.S. Republican President Donald Trump", "B": "Former Democratic President Barack Obama", "C": "His son Beau", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "How many Americans does cancer kill each year according to Biden?", "options": {"A": "600,000 Americans", "B": "6 million Americans", "C": "60,000 Americans", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What did Biden tell Obama he would have loved to be?", "options": {"A": "The president who presided over the end of cancer as we know it", "B": "The president who achieved world peace", "C": "The president who landed on the moon", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Why did Biden say he didn't run for president?", "options": {"A": "He did not have the stomach to run for president after his son's death", "B": "He did not agree with the current political climate", "C": "He was too busy with the Cancer Moonshot initiative", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What requirement did Biden mention for running for the presidency?", "options": {"A": "Being prepared to give every ounce of their energy", "B": "Having a clear political agenda", "C": "Having a significant amount of political experience", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who did Biden praise for working with Democrats on the fight against cancer?", "options": {"A": "Republicans", "B": "Independent parties", "C": "Foreign allies", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Which topic did Biden subtly criticize the Trump administration on?", "options": {"A": "Research on global warming", "B": "The Cancer Moonshot initiative", "C": "The approach to healthcare", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What did Biden say about the fight against cancer in America?", "options": {"A": "It's the only bipartisan thing left in America", "B": "It's being neglected by the current administration", "C": "It's a losing battle", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "Who was Joe Biden speaking to during his speech?", "options": {"A": "At the South by Southwest technology summit", "B": "At a Democratic party convention", "C": "In a televised interview", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "When did Biden's son Beau die?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "In 2015", "C": "In 2017", "D": "In 2013"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What initiative did Biden lead under former President Barack Obama?", "options": {"A": "Healthcare Reform", "B": "The Cancer Moonshot", "C": "Global Warming Action", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What emotion does Biden primarily express in his speech?", "options": {"A": "Excitement", "B": "Pride", "C": "Anger", "D": "Emotionality"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "What was Biden's reason for not running for president in 2015?", "options": {"A": "He didn't want to run against Donald Trump", "B": "He did not have the stomach to run for president after his son's death", "C": "He wanted to focus on his career", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What was Biden's regret, according to his conversation with Obama?", "options": {"A": "That he did not run for president", "B": "That he did not end cancer as we know it", "C": "That he had not done enough for cancer research", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Who did Biden suggest were not abiding by research on global warming?", "options": {"A": "Some in the new outfit", "B": "The current administration", "C": "Republicans", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who did Biden praise for their work against cancer?", "options": {"A": "Republicans", "B": "Democrats", "C": "Barack Obama", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Did Biden express a willingness to work with the current administration?", "options": {"A": "Yes", "B": "No", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "He did not specify"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "How many Americans are estimated to die from cancer each year, according to Biden's speech?", "options": {"A": "600,000", "B": "500,000", "C": "400,000", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}]}
{"passage": "WASHINGTON (Reuters) - Prospects dimmed on Monday for the U.S. House of Representatives to vote this week on Republican legislation to restrict gun sales to suspected extremists before Congress goes on a seven-week summer break.  Republicans including House Speaker Paul Ryan have been under pressure to act on gun legislation since the June 12 mass shootings at a gay nightclub in Orlando, Florida. Congress begins a summer recess on Friday. But with the House floor schedule filling with other bills, Republicans said gun legislation was unlikely to come up before September, when prospects for serious action could be overshadowed by the fall presidential election campaign.   Representative Jim Jordan of Ohio, who heads the conservative House Freedom Caucus, said, “I do not anticipate that bill.” The measure, backed by the National Rifle Association, would give government authorities three days to convince a judge to block the sale of weapons to someone suspected of involvement in violent extremism. But Ryan has been unable to win support from conservative Republicans who say the measure poses potential constitutional problems and should be subjected to regular legislative channels including formal hearings. Republican lawmakers say discussions aimed at finding compromise are continuing. But the measure did not come up at a Monday meeting with Republican leaders to discuss the week’s agenda, said another lawmaker who predicted it would not see a vote this week.   The stalemate leaves hanging Democratic demands for stronger gun restrictions, despite an unprecedented 25-hour sit-in by House Democrats last month, and sidelines any potential movement on an alternative bipartisan bill seen as a possible compromise. “A vote is going to be stalled” until Congress returns from its long summer break, one Republican aide said. Lawmakers initially believed Congress could pass some kind of measure before their summer recess after the Orlando shootings raised national security concerns and polls showed a majority of Americans in favor of greater restrictions. ", "QA1_list": [{"question": "When did the June 12 mass shootings occur at a gay nightclub in Orlando, Florida?", "options": {"A": "Before the summer recess", "B": "During the summer recess", "C": "After the summer recess", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who is the House Speaker under pressure to act on gun legislation?", "options": {"A": "Paul Ryan", "B": "Jim Jordan", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "The National Rifle Association"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who heads the conservative House Freedom Caucus?", "options": {"A": "Paul Ryan", "B": "Jim Jordan", "C": "The National Rifle Association", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Who backed the measure that would give government authorities three days to convince a judge to block the sale of weapons to someone suspected of involvement in violent extremism?", "options": {"A": "House Freedom Caucus", "B": "Republican lawmakers", "C": "The National Rifle Association", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "Why has Paul Ryan been unable to win support from conservative Republicans for the measure?", "options": {"A": "Because of the potential constitutional problems", "B": "Because of the Orlando shootings", "C": "Because of the summer recess", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What action did House Democrats take last month for stronger gun restrictions?", "options": {"A": "A sit-in", "B": "A protest", "C": "A strike", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "When is the vote going to be stalled according to one Republican aide?", "options": {"A": "Until Congress returns from its long summer break", "B": "Until the Orlando shootings case is closed", "C": "Until the fall presidential election campaign begins", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What did lawmakers initially believe about Congress passing some kind of measure?", "options": {"A": "It could pass before their summer recess", "B": "It could pass during their summer recess", "C": "It could pass after their summer recess", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Why did the Orlando shootings raise national security concerns?", "options": {"A": "Because the shootings occurred at a gay nightclub", "B": "Because a majority of Americans were in favor of greater restrictions", "C": "Because the shooter was suspected of involvement in violent extremism", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "What did polls show about a majority of Americans after the Orlando shootings?", "options": {"A": "They were in favor of greater gun restrictions", "B": "They were against gun restrictions", "C": "They were unaffected by the shootings", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "Why have Republicans, including House Speaker Paul Ryan been pressurized to act on gun legislation?", "options": {"A": "Due to an increase in violent extremism", "B": "After mass shootings at a gay nightclub in Orlando on June 12", "C": "Due the upcoming presidential elections", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "When does Congress begin its summer recess?", "options": {"A": "Monday", "B": "Friday", "C": "Saturday", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What will likely happen to gun legislation in September due to the presidential election campaign?", "options": {"A": "It will be passed urgently", "B": "It could be overshadowed", "C": "It will be a primary focus of discussion", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Who heads the conservative House Freedom Caucus?", "options": {"A": "Paul Ryan", "B": "Jim Jordan", "C": "The National Rifle Association", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What does the backed measure by the National Rifle Association entail?", "options": {"A": "Granting government authorities three days to convince a judge to block the sale of weapons to suspected extremists", "B": "Allowing the unrestricted sale of firearms to all American citizens", "C": "Supporting stronger gun restrictions", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Why has Paul Ryan been unable to win support from conservative Republicans on the measure?", "options": {"A": "Because the measure is not backed by the National Rifle Association", "B": "Due to potential constitutional problems associated with the measure", "C": "Because the measure entails a reduction in gun sales", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What unprecedented act did House Democrats undertake last month?", "options": {"A": "They went on a seven-week summer break", "B": "They started a 25-hour sit-in", "C": "They backed a measure by the National Rifle Association", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What is likely to occur to the vote on gun restriction measures during the summer break?", "options": {"A": "The vote will be accelerated", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "The vote will be stalled", "D": "The vote will be completed"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What belief was held by lawmakers before their summer recess?", "options": {"A": "Congress would reject any kind of gun restriction measure", "B": "Congress could pass some kind of gun restriction measure", "C": "The President would veto any kind of gun restriction measure", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What did the Orlando shootings raise?", "options": {"A": "National security concerns", "B": "Support for the National Rifle Association", "C": "Support for the Republican party", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}]}
{"passage": "  Optical tweezers microrheology (OTM) offers a powerful approach to probe the\nnonlinear response of complex soft matter systems, such as networks of\nentangled polymers, over wide-ranging spatiotemporal scales. OTM can also\nuniquely characterize the microstructural dynamics that lead to the intriguing\nnonlinear rheological properties that these systems exhibit. However, the\nstrain in OTM measurements, applied by optically forcing a micro-probe through\nthe material, induces network inhomogeneities in and around the strain path,\nand the resultant flow field complicates the measured response of the system.\nThrough a robust set of custom-designed OTM protocols, coupled with modeling\nand analytical calculations, we characterize the time-varying inhomogeneity\nfields induced by OTM measurements. We show that post-strain homogenization\ndoes not interfere with the intrinsic stress relaxation dynamics of the system,\nrather it manifests as an independent component in the stress decay, even in\nhighly nonlinear regimes such as with the microrheological-LAOS (mLAOS)\nprotocols we introduce. Our specific results show that Rouse-like elastic\nretraction, rather than disentanglement and disengagement, dominates the\nnonlinear stress relaxation of entangled polymers at micro- and meso- scales.\nThus, our study opens up possibilities of performing precision nonlinear\nmicrorheological measurements, such as mLAOS, on a wide range of complex\nmacromolecular systems.\n", "QA1_list": [{"question": "What does Optical tweezers microrheology (OTM) help to probe?", "options": {"A": "The nonlinear response of complex soft matter systems", "B": "The elasticity of various metals", "C": "The density of different gases", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What interferes with the intrinsic stress relaxation dynamics of the system as per the Optical tweezers microrheology (OTM)?", "options": {"A": "Post-strain homogenization", "B": "Pre-strain homogenization", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "The micro-probe"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What dominates the nonlinear stress relaxation of entangled polymers at micro- and meso- scales?", "options": {"A": "Rouse-like elastic retraction", "B": "Disentanglement and disengagement", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "Microstructural dynamics"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does the strain in OTM measurements induce?", "options": {"A": "Network inhomogeneities in and around the strain path", "B": "A significant change in temperature", "C": "A change in the size of the micro-probe", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What complicates the measured response of the system in OTM measurements?", "options": {"A": "The resultant flow field", "B": "The temperature of the system", "C": "The size of the micro-probe", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "How are the time-varying inhomogeneity fields induced by OTM measurements characterized?", "options": {"A": "Through a robust set of custom-designed OTM protocols, coupled with modeling and analytical calculations", "B": "By manually examining the system over time", "C": "Through external heat application", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does OTM uniquely characterize?", "options": {"A": "The microstructural dynamics that lead to the nonlinear rheological properties", "B": "The effect of temperature on various materials", "C": "The chemical composition of materials", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the significance of the study mentioned in the text?", "options": {"A": "It opens up possibilities of performing precision nonlinear microrheological measurements, such as mLAOS, on a wide range of complex macromolecular systems", "B": "It allows for the production of stronger materials", "C": "It leads to new methods of environmental conservation", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What part of the stress decay does post-strain homogenization manifest as?", "options": {"A": "An independent component", "B": "A dependent system", "C": "A secondary element", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What types of systems can be probed by OTM?", "options": {"A": "Networks of entangled polymers", "B": "Solid metal compounds", "C": "Gaseous compounds", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "What is the primary aim of Optical tweezers microrheology (OTM)?", "options": {"A": "To study the flight patterns of mosquitoes", "B": "To probe the nonlinear response of complex systems like entangled polymers", "C": "To assist in performing minor surgeries", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What do the resultant flow fields complicate in OTM measurements?", "options": {"A": "The measured response of the system", "B": "The manufacturing process of optical tweezers", "C": "The duties of the lab technicians", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the role of custom-designed OTM protocols in the study?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "Characterizing the color scheme of complex soft matter systems", "C": "Characterizing the time-varying inhomogeneity fields induced by OTM measurements", "D": "Determining the temperature of the lasers used"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "Which process dominates the stress relaxation of entangled polymers at small scales according to the study?", "options": {"A": "Rouse-like elastic retraction", "B": "Hookean-elastic pull", "C": "Newtonian-like resistance", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does not interfere with the intrinsic stress relaxation dynamics of the system, based on the study?", "options": {"A": "Post-strain homogenization", "B": "The introduction of foreign particles", "C": "The application of heat", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What kind of systems can precision nonlinear microrheological measurements be performed on?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "Complex macromolecular systems", "C": "Simple isotropic systems", "D": "One-dimensional dynamic systems"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What manifests as an independent component in the stress decay?", "options": {"A": "Network inhomogeneities", "B": "Post-strain homogenization", "C": "Strain fields", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What is one challenge in using OTM for probing the properties of complex systems?", "options": {"A": "The high cost of optical tweezers", "B": "The inhomogeneities induced in the strain path", "C": "The lack of trained personnel", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Why is the study significant?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "It found a cure for a rare disease", "C": "It provided a method for determining the age of fossils", "D": "It opens up possibilities of performing precision nonlinear microrheological measurements on a wide range"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "What are the mLAOS protocols referred to in the text?", "options": {"A": "Procedures for analyzing celestial bodies", "B": "Protocols for preventing data breaches", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "Microrheological Large Amplitude Oscillatory Shear protocols"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}]}
{"passage": "DUBAI (Reuters) - Saudi Arabia detained 11 princes, four current ministers and tens of former ministers in a probe by a new anti-corruption body headed by Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman, Saudi-owned Al Arabiya television reported. According to a senior Saudi official who declined to be identified under briefing rules, those detained include:  - Prince Alwaleed bin Talal, chairman of Kingdom Holding 4280.SE - Prince Miteb bin Abdullah, minister of the National Guard - Prince Turki bin Abdullah, former governor of Riyadh province - Khalid al-Tuwaijri, former chief of the Royal Court - Adel Fakeih, Minister of Economy and Planning - Ibrahim al-Assaf, former finance minister - Abdullah al-Sultan, commander of the Saudi navy - Bakr bin Laden, chairman of Saudi Binladin Group - Mohammad al-Tobaishi, former head of protocol at the Royal Court - Amr al-Dabbagh, former governor of Saudi Arabian General Investment Authority - Alwaleed al-Ibrahim, owner of television network MBC - Khalid al-Mulheim, former director-general at Saudi Arabian Airlines  - Saoud al-Daweesh , former chief executive of Saudi Telecom 7010.SE - Prince Turki bin Nasser, former head of the Presidency of Meteorology and Environment - Prince Fahad bin Abdullah bin Mohammad al-Saud, former deputy defence minister - Saleh Kamel, businessman - Mohammad al-Amoudi, businessman ", "QA1_list": [{"question": "Who headed the new anti-corruption body in Saudi Arabia?", "options": {"A": "Prince Alwaleed bin Talal", "B": "Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman", "C": "Prince Miteb bin Abdullah", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Who was the prince detained that used to be a minister of the National Guard?", "options": {"A": "Prince Alwaleed bin Talal", "B": "Prince Turki bin Nasser", "C": "Prince Miteb bin Abdullah", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "Who was detained in the probe that used to be the governor of Riyadh province?", "options": {"A": "Prince Turki bin Abdullah", "B": "Mohammad al-Tobaishi", "C": "Saoud al-Daweesh ", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who was the former chief of the Royal Court who got detained?", "options": {"A": "Khalid al-Tuwaijri", "B": "Ibrahim al-Assaf", "C": "Adel Fakeih", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who was the Minister of Economy and Planning that was detained by Saudi Arabia?", "options": {"A": "Prince Fahad bin Abdullah bin Mohammad al-Saud", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "Bakr bin Laden", "D": "Adel Fakeih"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "The detained person who used to be a finance minister is called?", "options": {"A": "Khalid al-Mulheim", "B": "Ibrahim al-Assaf", "C": "Mohammad al-Amoudi", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "The commander of the Saudi navy who was detained is called?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "Abdullah al-Sultan", "C": "Saleh Kamel", "D": "Alwaleed al-Ibrahim"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Who among the detainees was the former director-general at Saudi Arabian Airlines?", "options": {"A": "Khalid al-Mulheim", "B": "Saoud al-Daweesh ", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "Mohammad al-Amoudi"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who among the detainees used to be the chief executive of Saudi Telecom 7010.SE?", "options": {"A": "Amr al-Dabbagh", "B": "Mohammad al-Amoudi", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "Saoud al-Daweesh "}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "Who among the detainees was the former head of the Presidency of Meteorology and Environment?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "Prince Turki bin Nasser", "C": "Saleh Kamel", "D": "Mohammad al-Tobaishi"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "Who is heading the new anti-corruption body according to the report?", "options": {"A": "Prince Turki bin Nasser", "B": "Prince Alwaleed bin Talal", "C": "Prince Mohammed bin Salman", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "Which prominent businessman was among the detainees as per the report?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "Saleh Kamel", "C": "Prince Miteb bin Abdullah", "D": "Prince Turki bin Abdullah"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What position did Prince Miteb bin Abdullah hold?", "options": {"A": "Former governor of Saudi Arabian General Investment Authority", "B": "Owner of television network MBC", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "Minister of the National Guard"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "What role did Amr al-Dabbagh formerly serve in?", "options": {"A": "Former governor of Saudi Arabian General Investment Authority", "B": "Chairman of Kingdom Holding", "C": "Former finance minister", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who is the owner of the television network MBC?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "Amr al-Dabbagh", "C": "Mohammad al-Amoudi", "D": "Alwaleed al-Ibrahim"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "Who was the former chief of the Royal Court among the detainees?", "options": {"A": "Prince Fahad bin Abdullah bin Mohammad al-Saud", "B": "Khalid al-Tuwaijri", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "Ibrahim al-Assaf"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Who is the former head of protocol at the Royal Court among the detainees?", "options": {"A": "Mohammad al-Tobaishi", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "Khalid al-Mulheim", "D": "Abdullah al-Sultan"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who was the commander of the Saudi navy among the detainees?", "options": {"A": "Abdullah al-Sultan", "B": "Prince Turki bin Nasser", "C": "Khalid al-Mulheim", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who was the former director-general at Saudi Arabian Airlines among the detainees?", "options": {"A": "Mohammad al-Tobaishi", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "Khalid al-Mulheim", "D": "Ibrahim al-Assaf"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "Who is the chairman of Kingdom Holding among the detainees?", "options": {"A": "Prince Turki bin Nasser", "B": "Prince Alwaleed bin Talal", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "Mohammad al-Amoudi"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}]}
{"passage": "= Becket Hill State Park Reserve =\n\nBecket Hill State Park Reserve is a public recreation area lying adjacent to Nehantic State Forest in the town of Lyme , Connecticut , United States . The state park is listed by the Connecticut Department of Energy and Environmental Protection as an undeveloped , walk @-@ in park totaling 260 acres ( 110 ha ) with no officially listed activities . The park 's name is sometimes misspelled as Beckett Hill .\n\n= = History = =\n\nBecket Hill State Park Reserve is named for an early settler of the area named Becket and the land was part of the Nehantic tribe 's territory . This state park was acquired by the State of Connecticut in order to preserve the hill , but unlike the abutting Nehantic State Forest , Becket Hill has accessibility problems and is returning to its natural state . In 1961 , the land for the Becket Hill State Park Reserve was given to the State of Connecticut by the George Dudley Seymour Trust . Beckett Hill was first listed on the Connecticut Register and Manual for 1962 with its present 260 acres of undeveloped land . The Becket Hill State Park Reserve is the 76th designated Connecticut State Park .\n\n= = Activities = =\n\nThe reserve is an undeveloped , walk @-@ in park with access through the Lyme section of Nehantic State Forest , which is entered from Connecticut Route 156 . Bushwhacking is required as no roads or trails cross from the forest to the state park reserve . The reserve 's boundary with the state forest is created by 69 @-@ acre ( 28 ha ) Uncas Lake and Falls Brook , a stream that connects Uncas Lake with 30 @-@ acre ( 12 ha ) Norwich Pond . Boat launches for non @-@ motorized craft are located on each . The waters are stocked with brook , brown and rainbow trout by the State of Connecticut and other fish include largemouth bass , yellow perch and sunfish .\n\n", "QA1_list": [{"question": "Where is Becket Hill State Park Reserve located?", "options": {"A": "Lyme, Connecticut, United States", "B": "New Haven, Connecticut, United States", "C": "Hartford, Connecticut, United States", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the size of Becket Hill State Park Reserve?", "options": {"A": "260 acres", "B": "110 acres", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "500 acres"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What type of park is Becket Hill State Park Reserve described as by the Connecticut Department of Energy and Environmental Protection?", "options": {"A": "Developed park", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "Undeveloped, walk-in park", "D": "Forest reserve"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "Who was the park named after?", "options": {"A": "An early settler of the area named Becket", "B": "George Dudley Seymour", "C": "The Nehantic tribe", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who gave the land for the Becket Hill State Park Reserve to the State of Connecticut?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "The Nehantic tribe", "C": "The National Forest Service", "D": "The George Dudley Seymour Trust"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "When was Becket Hill State Park Reserve first listed on the Connecticut Register and Manual?", "options": {"A": "1962", "B": "1961", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "1970"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What types of fish does the State of Connecticut stock in the waters of the state park reserve?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "Sea bass, cod, and herring", "C": "Brook, brown and rainbow trout", "D": "Pike, salmon and eel"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What type of access to the park does the reserve offer?", "options": {"A": "Accessibility by vehicle", "B": "Accessible trails", "C": "Bushwhacking required", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "Which body of water serves as a boundary for the reserve and the Nehantic State Forest?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "Norwich Pond", "C": "Uncas Lake", "D": "Falls Brook"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What number is the Becket Hill State Park Reserve in the list of designated Connecticut State Parks?", "options": {"A": "76th", "B": "50th", "C": "100th", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "Who is Becket Hill State Park Reserve named after?", "options": {"A": "An early settler of the area named Becket", "B": "The Nehantic tribe who originally owned the land", "C": "George Dudley Seymour, the man who donated the land", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the state of Becket Hill State Park Reserve according to the Connecticut Department of Energy and Environmental Protection?", "options": {"A": "Fully developed", "B": "Under renovation", "C": "Under development", "D": "Undeveloped"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "How did the State of Connecticut acquire the land for Becket Hill State Park Reserve?", "options": {"A": "It was purchased from a private landowner", "B": "It was donated by the George Dudley Seymour Trust", "C": "It was seized as state land", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "How is access to Becket Hill State Park Reserve provided?", "options": {"A": "Through paved roads and clearly marked trails", "B": "Through the Lyme section of Nehantic State Forest", "C": "Directly from Connecticut Route 156", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What kind of wildlife can you find in Becket Hill State Park Reserve?", "options": {"A": "Brook, brown and rainbow trout, largemouth bass, yellow perch and sunfish", "B": "Gizzly bears, beaver, and moose", "C": "No animals are found in the park", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the size of Becket Hill State Park Reserve?", "options": {"A": "76 hectares", "B": "110 hectares", "C": "260 acres", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What type of area is Becket Hill State Park Reserve listed as?", "options": {"A": "A recreational spot", "B": "Walk-in park", "C": "National monument", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Where exactly is Becket Hill State Park Reserve located?", "options": {"A": "In the city of New Haven, Connecticut", "B": "Adjacent to Nehantic State Forest in the town of Lyme, Connecticut", "C": "In the city of Hartford, Connecticut", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "When was the land for the Becket Hill State Park Reserve given to the State of Connecticut?", "options": {"A": "In 1961", "B": "In 1861", "C": "In 1951", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What bodies of water lie adjacent to the reserve?", "options": {"A": "Uncas Lake and Falls Brook", "B": "Norwich Pond and Nehantic River", "C": "The Connecticut River and the Atlantic Ocean", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}]}
{"passage": "  We investigate the effects of gravitational lensing in the binary pulsar\nsystem J0737-3039. Current measurement of the orbital inclination allows the\nmillisecond pulsar (A) to pass very close (at R_{min}=4000 km) in projection to\nthe companion pulsar (B), with R_{min} comparable to the Einstein radius (2600\nkm). For this separation at the conjunction, lensing causes small (about 10%)\nmagnification of the pulsar A signal on a timescale of several seconds, and\ndisplaces the pulsar image on the sky plane by about 1200 km. More importantly,\nlensing introduces a correction (of several microsec) to the conventional\nShapiro delay formula used in pulsar timing analysis, and gives rise to a\ngeometric time delay together with the delays associated with the pulsar spin\nperiod. These lensing effects can influence the determination of the system\nparameters by both timing and scintillation studies. Given the current\nuncertainty in the orbital inclination, more extreme manifestations of lensing\n(e.g. magnification by a factor of several) are possible. We compare our\npredictions with the existing observations and discuss the possibility of\ndetecting gravitational lensing signatures in the system. The anomalously high\npoint in A's lightcurve close to superior conjunction might be caused by\ngravitational lensing.\n", "QA1_list": [{"question": "What is the primary object of investigation in the study described in the text?", "options": {"A": "Gravitational lensing effects in the binary pulsar system J0737-3039", "B": "The anomaly in A's lightcurve", "C": "The study of magnification by gravitational lensing", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the orbital inclination measurement referenced in the text?", "options": {"A": "Unanswerable", "B": "Several microsec", "C": "4000 km", "D": "2600 km"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "When pulsar A passes very close to pulsar B, what is the approximate distance in projection?", "options": {"A": "2600 km", "B": "4000 km", "C": "1200 km", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What is the magnitude of magnification that lensing induces on the signal of pulsar A?", "options": {"A": "10%", "B": "Several microns", "C": "Several seconds", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "How long does the magnification of the pulsar A signal induced by lensing last?", "options": {"A": "Several seconds", "B": "Several microns", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "1200 km"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "How much does lensing displace the pulsar image on the sky plane?", "options": {"A": "2600 km", "B": "1200 km", "C": "4000 km", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What does lensing introduce a correction to?", "options": {"A": "The conventional Shapiro delay formula used in pulsar timing analysis", "B": "The distance between pulsar A and B", "C": "The Einstein radius", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What might the anomaly in A's lightcurve be caused by?", "options": {"A": "Gravitational lensing", "B": "The Shapiro delay", "C": "The distance between pulsar A and B", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What do lensing effects potentially influence in the binary pulsar system J0737-3039?", "options": {"A": "The determination of the system parameters by both timing and scintillation studies", "B": "The projection distance between pulsar A and B", "C": "The Einstein radius", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "According to the text, what are the possible extreme manifestations of lensing, given the current uncertainty in the orbital inclination?", "options": {"A": "Magnification by a factor of several", "B": "A reduction in the Einstein radius", "C": "The delay in pulsar spin period", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "What is being investigated in the binary pulsar system J0737-3039?", "options": {"A": "The effects of gravitational lensing", "B": "The effects of cosmic radiation", "C": "The effects of black holes", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the approximate distance in km of the minimum separation (R_{min}) between the millisecond pulsar (A) and the companion pulsar (B)?", "options": {"A": "4000 km", "B": "2600 km", "C": "1200 km", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Which pulsar passes very close to the other in the system?", "options": {"A": "Pulsar A", "B": "Pulsar B", "C": "Both A and B", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What approximate percentage magnification does lensing cause on the pulsar A signal?", "options": {"A": "10%", "B": "50%", "C": "25%", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does lensing introduce in addition to a geometric time delay in the system?", "options": {"A": "A correction to the conventional Shapiro delay formula", "B": "A signal distortion in Pulsar A", "C": "An increase in the system's orbital speed", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What can the lensing effects potentially influence?", "options": {"A": "The determination of the system parameters", "B": "The appearance of the binary pulsar", "C": "The formation of new species", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What could be a cause of the anomalously high point in A's lightcurve close to superior conjunction?", "options": {"A": "Gravitational lensing", "B": "Nuclear fusion inside the neutron star", "C": "Intense solar winds hitting the pulsar", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Under what circumstance are more extreme manifestations of lensing possible in the pulsar system?", "options": {"A": "Given the current uncertainty in the orbital inclination", "B": "If the system is at a high altitude", "C": "If there is a bigger pulsar in close proximity", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "About how much does lensing displace the pulsar image on the sky plane?", "options": {"A": "1200 km", "B": "4000 km", "C": "2600 km", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What tool is typically used to determine system parameters that the lensing effects could influence?", "options": {"A": "Timing and scintillation studies", "B": "The use of complex equations", "C": "Space observation telescopes", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}]}
{"passage": "= ( ( â 27 ) 2 / 3 ) 3 / 2 =\n93 / 2 = 27 is clearly wrong . The problem here occurs in taking the positive square root rather than the negative one at the last step , but in general the same sorts of problems occur as described for complex numbers in the section Â§ Failure of power and logarithm identities .\n\n= = Real exponents = =\n\nThe identities and properties shown above for integer exponents are true for positive real numbers with non @-@ integer exponents as well . However the identity\n<formula>\ncannot be extended consistently to cases where b is a negative real number ( see Â§ Real exponents with negative bases ) . The failure of this identity is the basis for the problems with complex number powers detailed under Â§ Failure of power and logarithm identities .\nExponentiation to real powers of positive real numbers can be defined either by extending the rational powers to reals by continuity , or more usually as given in Â§ Powers via logarithms below .\n\n= = = Limits of rational exponents = = =\n\nSince any irrational number can be expressed as the limit of a sequence of rational numbers , exponentiation of a positive real number b with an arbitrary real exponent x can be defined by continuity with the rule\n<formula>\nwhere the limit as r gets close to x is taken only over rational values of r . This limit only exists for positive b . The ( Îµ , Î´ ) -definition of limit is used , this involves showing that for any desired accuracy of the result bx one can choose a sufficiently small interval around x so all the rational powers in the interval are within the desired accuracy .\nFor example , if x", "QA1_list": [{"question": "Where does the problem occur in the equation = ( ( â 27 ) 2 / 3 ) 3 / 2 =?", "options": {"A": "Taking the positive square root in the last step", "B": "Taking the negative square root in the first step", "C": "Multiplying the numbers instead of dividing", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is true for positive real numbers with non-integer exponents?", "options": {"A": "The identities and properties for integer exponents don't apply", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "They cannot be expressed as the limit of a sequence of rational numbers", "D": "The identities and properties shown for integer exponents are also true"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "Can the identity <formula> be consistently extended where b is a negative real number?", "options": {"A": "Yes, but it changes the outcome", "B": "No", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "Yes, without any changes to the outcome"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "How can exponentiation to real powers of positive real numbers be defined?", "options": {"A": "By limiting the rational powers to integers", "B": "By adding all the rational exponents together", "C": "By extending the rational powers to reals by continuity, or as given in Powers via logarithms", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "How can an irrational number be expressed?", "options": {"A": "As the product of two rational numbers", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "As the sum of two rational numbers", "D": "As the limit of a sequence of rational numbers"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "What is required for the limit as r gets close to x but only over rational values of r?", "options": {"A": "The number b must be negative", "B": "The number b must be positive", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "The number b can be either positive or negative"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What does the ( Îµ , Î´ ) -definition of limit involve?", "options": {"A": "Showing that for any accuracy of bx, a sufficiently small interval around x can be chosen", "B": "Calculating the limit as x approaches infinity", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "Dividing the result by the number of rational powers in the interval"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the basis for the problems with complex number powers?", "options": {"A": "The failure of the identity <formula>", "B": "The success of the identity <formula>", "C": "The non-integer number b", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the problem with the equation 93 / 2 = 27?", "options": {"A": "The problem lies in taking the positive square root", "B": "The problem lies in the division step", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "The problem lies in the multiplication step"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the default definition used for defining the limit in rational exponents?", "options": {"A": "The ( Îµ , Î´ ) -definition of limit", "B": "The Pythagorean theorem", "C": "Euler's formula", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "Where does the problem occur when taking the square root of -27?", "options": {"A": "In choosing the positive square root over the negative one", "B": "In considering the square root to be a real number", "C": "In taking the square of 27", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What kinds of problems occur with complex numbers?", "options": {"A": "In the application of power and logarithm identities", "B": "In the application of division and multiplication principles", "C": "In the consideration of the real and imaginary parts", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Can the identity for a positive real number with non-integer exponents be consistently extended to cases where b is a negative real number?", "options": {"A": "Yes, it can be consistently extended", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "No, it cannot be consistently extended", "D": "It can be extended only in some cases"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "How can exponentiation to real powers of positive real numbers be defined?", "options": {"A": "By extending the negative powers to reals", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "By extending the rational powers to reals by continuity", "D": "By limiting the irrational powers to rational ones"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "Can an irrational number be expressed as the limit of a sequence of rational numbers?", "options": {"A": "No, irrational numbers cannot be expressed in terms of rational numbers", "B": "Yes, any irrational number can be expressed as the limit of a sequence of rational numbers", "C": "Only some irrational numbers can be expressed as the limit of a sequence of rational numbers", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Can the equation with real exponent x be defined by continuity with the rule of limit?", "options": {"A": "Yes, it can be defined by continuity with the rule of limit", "B": "No, it cannot be defined by continuity with the rule of limit", "C": "It can be defined by continuity only in some cases", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Does the limit only exist for positive b?", "options": {"A": "No, it exists for both positive and negative", "B": "Yes, it only exists for positive b", "C": "Yes, it only exists for negative b", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What definition of limit is used while defining the continuity for the real exponent x?", "options": {"A": "The (Îµ, Î´)-definition of limit", "B": "The (Îµ, Îº)-definition of limit", "C": "The (Îµ, Î³)-definition of limit", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does the (Îµ, Î´)-definition of limit involve?", "options": {"A": "Involves showing that the result bx can be achieved with any desired accuracy", "B": "Involves choosing a sufficiently small interval around x", "C": "Involves showing all rational powers in the interval are within the desired accuracy", "D": "All of the above"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "In the failure of power and logarithm identities, what is primarily considered?", "options": {"A": "Failure of the identity due to negative real number bases", "B": "Failure of the identity due to positive real number bases", "C": "Failure of the identity due to irrational real number bases", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}]}
{"passage": "WASHINGTON (Reuters) - U.S. regulations, proposed by the Treasury to crack down on companies that try to reduce taxes by rebasing abroad, have begun a White House review and could be finalized shortly, officials said on Tuesday. The regulations, which would make it difficult for U.S. business operations to avoid taxation while shifting profits overseas through a practice called “earnings stripping,” were received by the White House Office of Management and Budget (OMB) last week. The agency has up to 90 days to decide whether the rules should be finalized or returned to Treasury for further consideration. “We are satisfied we have addressed stakeholder feedback and are close to issuing final earnings stripping regulations,” a Treasury spokesperson said. The Obama administration has faced widespread criticism from the business community over its regulatory assault on tax inversions, which are tax-driven mergers in which a U.S. company acquires a smaller, foreign business in a low-tax country and shifts its headquarters there, if only on paper, to avoid higher U.S. taxes.    Business and industry groups have threatened lawsuits and called for the new rules to be withdrawn or heavily revised because of what critics say is the potential for unintended harm to business. Members of Congress have also accused the administration of overstepping its legal authority. Earnings stripping occurs when an inverted company eludes U.S. taxes on its domestic operation by shifting profits overseas in the form of tax-deductible interest payments to its foreign parent. The new rules would change certain interest payments into equity dividends, which are not tax deductible in the United States.  The regulations were proposed in April, along with a temporary rule to prevent serial inversion deals by foreign companies. That rule, which is already the target of a lawsuit, has not yet been forwarded to OMB. ", "QA1_list": [{"question": "What is the purpose of the regulations proposed by the U.S. Treasury?", "options": {"A": "To reduce taxes for companies", "B": "To prevent companies from reducing taxes by rebasing abroad", "C": "To increase taxes for foreign companies", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What is the practice of 'earnings stripping'?", "options": {"A": "A company decreasing its profits to pay less taxes", "B": "A U.S. business operation shifting profits overseas to avoid taxation", "C": "A method of calculating business profits", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "How long does the White House Office of Management and Budget have to decide on the rules?", "options": {"A": "60 days", "B": "90 days", "C": "30 days", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What is a tax inversion?", "options": {"A": "A tax-driven merger between two U.S. companies", "B": "A U.S. company acquiring a larger foreign business", "C": "A U.S. company acquiring a smaller foreign business to shift its headquarters to a low-tax country", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "Who criticized the Obama administration's assault on tax inversions?", "options": {"A": "The Treasury Department", "B": "Congress and the business community", "C": "Foreign businesses", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What is the proposed change to the new rules concerning tax-deductible interest payments?", "options": {"A": "The new rules would keep tax-deductible interest payments as they are", "B": "The new rules would increase tax-deductible interest payments", "C": "The new rules would change certain tax-deductible interest payments into equity dividends", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "When were the regulations proposed?", "options": {"A": "In April", "B": "In March", "C": "In May", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the purpose of the temporary rule proposed in April?", "options": {"A": "To prevent tax inversions", "B": "To prevent serial inversion deals by foreign companies", "C": "To increase taxation on lucrative businesses", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What legal action has been threatened over the new rules?", "options": {"A": "Petitions", "B": "Protests", "C": "Lawsuits", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What does an inverted company do to elude U.S. taxes?", "options": {"A": "Increases its domestic operation profits", "B": "Shifts its profits overseas in the form of tax-deductible interest payments to its foreign parent", "C": "Decreases its foreign operation profits", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "Who proposed the regulations to avoid tax reduction by U.S. companies rebasing abroad?", "options": {"A": "The Treasury", "B": "The White House Office of Management and Budget", "C": "The business community", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the purpose of these proposed regulations?", "options": {"A": "To encourage companies to move abroad", "B": "To make it difficult for U.S. business operations to avoid taxation while shifting profits overseas", "C": "To promote tax evasion", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Which agency has the authority to decide whether the rules should be finalized or returned to Treasury for further consideration?", "options": {"A": "The business community", "B": "The Congress", "C": "The White House Office of Management and Budget", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What are tax inversions?", "options": {"A": "Tax-driven mergers in which a U.S. company acquires a smaller, foreign business in a low-tax country and shifts its headquarters there", "B": "Tax reduction measures taken by the U.S. government", "C": "Tax evasion practices by foreign companies in the U.S.", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What technique is used by a company to elude U.S. taxes on its domestic operation, according to the text?", "options": {"A": "Tax evasion", "B": "Tax refund", "C": "Earnings stripping", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "How will the new rules potentially change the tax obligations of companies?", "options": {"A": "The rules will increase tax deductions", "B": "The rules will change certain interest payments into equity dividends, which are not tax deductible in the U.S. ", "C": "The rules will allow companies to move their headquarters abroad without any tax implications", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Who has accused the administration of overstepping its legal authority?", "options": {"A": "Foreign companies", "B": "Congress", "C": "Treasury", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Why did the business community criticize these regulations?", "options": {"A": "Because they were promoting tax evasion", "B": "Because they were restricting corporate growth", "C": "Because of the potential for unintended harm to business", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "When were these regulations proposed?", "options": {"A": "In January", "B": "In April", "C": "In June", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Why have business and industry groups threatened lawsuits?", "options": {"A": "Because they do not agree with the temporary rule to prevent serial inversion deals by foreign companies", "B": "Because they would oppose any regulation that would restrict their operations", "C": "Over concerns of what critics say is the potential for unintended harm to business", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}]}
{"passage": "= Genetic code =\n\nThe genetic code is the set of rules by which information encoded within genetic material ( DNA or mRNA sequences ) is translated into proteins by living cells . Translation is accomplished by the ribosome , which links amino acids in an order specified by mRNA , using transfer RNA ( tRNA ) molecules to carry amino acids and to read the mRNA three nucleotides at a time . The genetic code is highly similar among all organisms and can be expressed in a simple table with 64 entries .\nThe code defines how sequences of nucleotide triplets , called codons , specify which amino acid will be added next during protein synthesis . With some exceptions , a three @-@ nucleotide codon in a nucleic acid sequence specifies a single amino acid . Because the vast majority of genes are encoded with exactly the same code ( see the RNA codon table ) , this particular code is often referred to as the canonical or standard genetic code , or simply the genetic code , though in fact some variant codes have evolved . For example , protein synthesis in human mitochondria relies on a genetic code that differs from the standard genetic code .\nWhile the \" genetic code \" determines a protein 's amino acid sequence , other genomic regions determine when and where these proteins are produced according to a multitude of more complex \" gene regulatory codes \" .\n\n= = Discovery = =\n\nSerious efforts to understand how proteins are encoded began after the structure of DNA was discovered in 1953 . George Gamow postulated that sets of three bases must be employed to encode the 20 standard amino acids used by living cells to build proteins . With four different nucleotides , a code of 2 nucleotides would allow for only a maximum of 42", "QA1_list": [{"question": "What does the genetic code define?", "options": {"A": "How sequences of nucleotide triplets specify which amino acid will be added next during protein synthesis", "B": "How DNA sequences are translated into proteins", "C": "How ribosomes link amino acids", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What carries amino acids and reads the mRNA three nucleotides at a time?", "options": {"A": "The ribosome", "B": "The genetic material", "C": "Transfer RNA (tRNA) molecules", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What specifies a single amino acid?", "options": {"A": "A three nucleotide codon in a nucleic acid sequence", "B": "A variety of different codons", "C": "Gene regulatory codes", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "When were serious efforts to understand how proteins are encoded initiated?", "options": {"A": "1953", "B": "1960", "C": "1903", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who postulated that sets of three bases must be employed to encode the 20 standard amino acids?", "options": {"A": "George Gamow", "B": "James Watson", "C": "Rosalind Franklin", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What differentiates human mitochondria's protein synthesis from the standard genetic code?", "options": {"A": "It uses a distinct codon for each amino acid", "B": "It relies on a different genetic code", "C": "It uses a four nucleotide code", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What is the maximum number of combinations possible with a code of 2 nucleotides?", "options": {"A": "42 combinations", "B": "20 combinations", "C": "64 combinations", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is referred to as the canonical or standard genetic code?", "options": {"A": "The specific code that the majority of genes are encoded with", "B": "A code that consists of two nucleotides", "C": "The code used by human mitochondria", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What determines when and where the proteins encoded by the genetic code are produced?", "options": {"A": "Other genomic regions", "B": "The ribosome", "C": "The process of translation", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What is the role of the ribosome in regards to the genetic code?", "options": {"A": "Links amino acids in an order specified by mRNA", "B": "Carries amino acids and reads mRNA", "C": "Specifies a single amino acid", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "What is the genetic code responsible for?", "options": {"A": "Translating information encoded within genetic material into proteins", "B": "Determining the structure of DNA", "C": "Controlling the functions of the ribosome", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What do nucleotide triplets, called codons, specify?", "options": {"A": "When proteins are produced", "B": "The type of cell that will be produced", "C": "Which amino acid will be added next during protein synthesis", "D": "The behavior of genes"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "How are variant codes of the genetic code unique compared to the standard code?", "options": {"A": "They determine when a protein is produced", "B": "They have more than 64 entries", "C": "They differ in how they specify amino acids", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "How are the genetic regulatory codes more complex than the genetic code?", "options": {"A": "They contain more than three nucleotides", "B": "They determine when and where proteins are produced", "C": "They are responsible for the structure of DNA", "D": "They carry amino acids"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What was George Gamow's postulate about encoding the 20 standard amino acids?", "options": {"A": "Sets of two bases must be used", "B": "Nucleotide triplets must be used", "C": "Sets of three bases must be employed", "D": "Only one type of nucleotide can be used"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What is an example of an organism with a genetic code that differs from the standard genetic code?", "options": {"A": "Human mitochondria", "B": "Insects", "C": "Plants", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What function does transfer RNA (tRNA) have in translation?", "options": {"A": "It links amino acids", "B": "It carries amino acids and reads the mRNA three nucleotides at a time", "C": "It encodes the 20 standard amino acids", "D": "It controls the production of proteins"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What happens to the amino acid sequence if the genetic code changes?", "options": {"A": "The RNA codon table changes", "B": "The protein's amino acid sequence is affected", "C": "The number of nucleotides decreases", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What does a codon consist of in a nucleic acid sequence?", "options": {"A": "A single nucleotide", "B": "Two nucleotides", "C": "A single amino acid", "D": "Three nucleotides"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "What led to serious efforts to understand protein encoding?", "options": {"A": "The discovery of the RNA codon table", "B": "The discovery of the structure of DNA in 1953", "C": "The postulation of George Gamow about the genetic code", "D": "The discovery of amino acids in human mitochondria"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}]}
{"passage": "JUBA (Reuters) - Six aid workers kidnapped by rebels in South Sudan earlier this week have been released, according to the United Nations and a spokesman for the rebels.  The aid workers are from the French organization Solidarites International and had been kidnapped on Sunday while traveling on a road near the city of Raja, in the west of the country.   All of them were released and they have landed safely in Wau,  another city in the west of the country, a United Nations official in Juba who spoke on condition of anonymity told Reuters. He said one of those who had been held by the rebels was a foreigner.  Rebel spokesman Lam Paul Gabriel told Reuters that the six humanitarian aid workers had been freed:  All their belongings were given back to them including their vehicles.  It was not clear why the rebels had taken the aid workers and their vehicles into custody. Solidarites said in a statement on Monday that it had lost contact with three members of its team on Saturday. [L8N1OI50M] It gave no indication of their fate and it was not immediately clear why it gave a different number of those involved.  The spokesman for Solidarites in Paris did not immediately respond to a request for comment on the announcement of the release of its staff. The army spokesman in Juba also did not respond to request for comment. South Sudan is one of the world s most dangerous countries for aid workers. Some 28 aid workers have been killed this year, with nine shot dead in November alone, according to the United Nations. The world s youngest nation is embroiled in a civil war that has killed tens of thousands of people and forced a third of the 12 million strong population to flee their homes.  ", "QA1_list": [{"question": "Where were the kidnapped aid workers from?", "options": {"A": "United States", "B": "French organization Solidarites International", "C": "British organization Oxfam", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Where were the aid workers when they were kidnapped?", "options": {"A": "Juba", "B": "In a city in the east of the country", "C": "Near the city of Raja, in the west of the country", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "Where did the aid workers land after their release?", "options": {"A": "Raja", "B": "Juba", "C": "Paris", "D": "Wau, another city in the west of the country"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "Who confirmed the release of the kidnapped aid workers?", "options": {"A": "A United Nations official in Juba", "B": "Aid workers' families", "C": "The army spokesman in Juba", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "Who kidnapped the aid workers?", "options": {"A": "Unidentified persons", "B": "Rebels in South Sudan", "C": "Government officials", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Who was among those kidnapped?", "options": {"A": "A foreigner", "B": "South Sudanese citizens only", "C": "Rebel soldiers", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What was the condition of the belongings of the released aid workers?", "options": {"A": "They caught fire during captivity", "B": "They got drowned in a river", "C": "All their belongings were given back to them", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What is the internal conflict status of South Sudan?", "options": {"A": "Peaceful and stable", "B": "Embroiled in a civil war", "C": "Facing economic depression", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "How many aid workers were killed in South Sudan in November?", "options": {"A": "Nine", "B": "Three", "C": "Twenty eight", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "How many people from South Sudan's population have been forced to flee their homes?", "options": {"A": "Approximately a quarter of the 12 million population", "B": "Unanswerable", "C": "Approximately a third of the 12 million population", "D": "Half of the 12 million population"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "Who were the victims of the kidnapping?", "options": {"A": "Aid workers from Solidarites International", "B": "Aid workers from the United Nations", "C": "Government officials from the city of Raja", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "According to the text, where were the six aid workers when they were kidnapped?", "options": {"A": "In Paris", "B": "In Wau", "C": "Near the city of Raja, in the west of the country", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "Where were the kidnapped aid workers released?", "options": {"A": "In the city of Raja", "B": "In Wau, another city in the west of the country", "C": "In Juba", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "How can the situation in South Sudan be best described?", "options": {"A": "It's relatively peaceful with occasional incidents", "B": "Violence is widespread, making it a dangerous place for aid workers", "C": "It's one of the safest countries for aid workers", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Was there any indication about the fate of the workers from Solidarites when they lost contact?", "options": {"A": "Yes, Solidarites were able to contact the kidnapped workers", "B": "No, they gave no indication of their fate", "C": "Solidarites claimed the workers were unharmed", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "Who released the information about the freeing of the kidnapped aid workers?", "options": {"A": "The rebels", "B": "Solidarites International", "C": "Both the United Nations and a spokesman for the rebels", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What was returned to the aid workers upon their release?", "options": {"A": "Only their personal belongings", "B": "Their belongings and their vehicles", "C": "Only their vehicles", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What is the reason mentioned in the text for the kidnapping of the aid workers?", "options": {"A": "Rebels wanted to make a political statement", "B": "The reason is not clear", "C": "They were mistaken for government officials", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What has forced a third of the 12 million strong population to abandon their homes?", "options": {"A": "A civil war", "B": "Extreme poverty", "C": "A massive natural disaster", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What was Solidarites' immediate response to the announcement of the release of its staff?", "options": {"A": "It confirmed the news and thanked the rebels", "B": "Its spokesperson in Paris did not immediately respond", "C": "It denied the reports of the workers' release", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}]}
{"passage": "  Cities have recognized the local impact of small craft breweries, in many\nways altering municipal codes to make it easier to establish breweries and\nmaking them the anchor points of economic development and revitalization.\nNevertheless, we do not know the extent to which these strategies impacted\nchanges at the neighborhood level across the nation. In this chapter, we\nexamine the relationship between growth and locations of craft breweries and\nthe incidence of neighborhood change across the United States. In the first\npart of the chapter, we rely on a unique dataset of geocoded brewery locations\nthat tracks openings and closings from 2004 to the present. Using measures of\nneighborhood change often found in literature on gentrification-related topics,\nwe develop statistical models relying on census tract demographic and\nemployment data to determine the extent to which brewery locations are\nassociated with social and demographic shifts since 2000. The strongest\npredictor of whether a craft brewery opened in 2013 or later in a neighborhood\nwas the presence of a prior brewery. We do not find evidence entirely\nconsistent with the common narrative of a link between gentrification and craft\nbrewing, but we see a link between an influx of lower-to-middle income urban\ncreatives and the introduction of a craft breweries. We advocate for urban\nplanners to recognize the importance of craft breweries in neighborhood\nrevitalization while also protecting residents from potential displacement.\n", "QA1_list": [{"question": "What is the strongest predictor of whether a craft brewery opened in 2013 or later in a neighborhood?", "options": {"A": "The presence of lower-to-middle income urban creatives", "B": "The presence of a prior brewery", "C": "The presence of a gentrified environment", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What kind of relationship does the chapter examine?", "options": {"A": "The relationship between growth and locations of craft breweries and the incidence of neighborhood change", "B": "The relationship between urban creatives and the introduction of craft breweries", "C": "The relationship between gentrification and craft brewing", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "During what years does the unique dataset track brewery openings and closings?", "options": {"A": "2000 to the present", "B": "2004 to the present", "C": "2013 onwards", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What has been the local impact of small craft breweries?", "options": {"A": "They have led to an influx of urban creatives", "B": "They have caused gentrification", "C": "They have been the anchor points of economic development and revitalization", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What do the authors suggest for urban planners?", "options": {"A": "To recognize the importance of craft breweries in neighborhood revitalization while also protecting residents from potential displacement", "B": "To establish more craft breweries", "C": "To change municipal codes to make it easier to establish breweries", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does the data fail to provide consistent evidence for?", "options": {"A": "A link between gentrification and craft brewing", "B": "The impact of craft breweries on social and demographic shifts", "C": "The role of urban creatives in establishing craft breweries", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What was seen in connection with the introduction of craft breweries?", "options": {"A": "A link between an influx of lower-to-middle income urban creatives", "B": "An increase in gentrification", "C": "A decrease in neighborhood revitalization", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What changes have cities recognized to be an impact of small craft breweries?", "options": {"A": "Their role in the gentrification of neighborhoods", "B": "Their influence on the local economy and neighborhood revitalization", "C": "Their contribution to an increase in urban creatives", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What is used in the development of the statistical models?", "options": {"A": "Census tract demographic and employment data", "B": "Data on the number of urban creatives", "C": "Data on gentrification-related topics", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What do the statistical models determine?", "options": {"A": "The extent to which brewery locations are associated with social and demographic shifts since 2000", "B": "The relationship between gentrification and craft brewing", "C": "The impact of brewery locations on gentrification indicators", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}], "QA2_list": [{"question": "What have cities recognized about the impact of small craft breweries?", "options": {"A": "Their role in increasing crime rates", "B": "Their contribution to environmental degradation", "C": "Their potential for boosting local economy and urban development", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What is the strongest predictor of a craft brewery opening in a neighborhood in 2013 or later?", "options": {"A": "The presence of a prior brewery", "B": "The number of existing retail establishments", "C": "The median household income", "D": "The population density"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What measures did the data rely on to develop statistical models?", "options": {"A": "Census tract demographic and employment data", "B": "Income and education level statistics", "C": "Development spending and urban planning data", "D": "National housing prices and rentals data"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What kind of demographic were found to instigate the introduction of craft breweries?", "options": {"A": "Higher-income professionals", "B": "Lower-income service industry workers", "C": "Unanswerable", "D": "Lower-to-middle income urban creatives"}, "correctAnswer": "D"}, {"question": "According to the text, how have municipalities responded to the growth of craft breweries?", "options": {"A": "They have made it more difficult for breweries to establish themselves", "B": "They have ignored their presence and potential impact", "C": "They have altered municipal codes to make it easier to establish breweries", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}, {"question": "What do the authors advocate for urban planners in the text?", "options": {"A": "Recognize the importance of craft breweries in neighborhood revitalization while also protecting residents from potential displacement", "B": "Invest in other industries besides craft breweries", "C": "Discourage the opening of new craft breweries to prevent overwhelming competition", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What was the period examined in the dataset of geocoded brewery locations used in the study?", "options": {"A": "2000 to the present", "B": "2004 to the present", "C": "2010 to the present", "D": "1995 to the present"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What does the common narrative suggest about gentrification and craft brewing?", "options": {"A": "There is a strong link between gentrification and craft brewing", "B": "Gentrification is causing the decline of craft brewing", "C": "Craft brewing is leading to de-gentrification", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "A"}, {"question": "What does the study find with regards to the narrative of a link between gentrification and craft brewing?", "options": {"A": "It finds the narrative to be entirely consistent", "B": "It does not find evidence entirely consistent with the narrative", "C": "It debunks the narrative entirely", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "B"}, {"question": "What kind of connection is observed between the arrival of lower-to-middle income urban creatives and craft breweries?", "options": {"A": "A decrease in the number of craft breweries", "B": "No noticeable relationship", "C": "A link between the arrival of these creatives and the introduction of craft breweries", "D": "Unanswerable"}, "correctAnswer": "C"}]}
